,geo,Tweets,User,Location,entities,sentiment,Country
0,,#Newsoftheday - Discover today's front pages of the #BelgianPress 🧐💡📰!#Tourism #hazard #kompany #coronavirus… ,Auxipress,Belgium,"[('today', 'DATE'), ('Tourism', 'PERSON'), '']","{'neg': 0.0, 'neu': 1.0, 'pos': 0.0, 'compound': 0.0}",Belgium
1,," Iran: #Coronavirus Update, Over 44,800 Deaths, May 27, 2020, 6:00 PM CEST - NCRI  #HumanRightsV…",davedaram,,"[('Iran', 'GPE'), ('Over 44,800', 'CARDINAL'), ('May 27, 2020', 'DATE'), ('6:00 PM', 'TIME'), ('CEST', 'PERSON'), ('HumanRightsV', 'PERSON')]","{'neg': 0.0, 'neu': 1.0, 'pos': 0.0, 'compound': 0.0}",
2,, #Coronavirus has not stopped Modi-Shah's police to target Muslim students for participating in anti-citizenship act protest!!…,israrul8,,"[('Coronavirus', 'PERSON'), (""Modi-Shah's"", 'ORG'), ('Muslim', 'NORP')]","{'neg': 0.0, 'neu': 0.87, 'pos': 0.13, 'compound': 0.3071}",
3,, Does anyone still read the #NYT ? 🤣🤣“The New York Times admitted this week the doctor didn’t die and didn’t have coronavirus…,Aliciastarr001,California (Bay Area),"[('🤣🤣', 'PERSON'), ('The New York Times', 'ORG'), ('this week', 'DATE')]","{'neg': 0.16, 'neu': 0.782, 'pos': 0.058, 'compound': -0.5423}",USA
4,," Those on the front lines of the COVID-19 fight need quick, easy access to real-time critical data. That’s what APIs (and AP…",sounakpal,India,"[('AP', 'ORG')]","{'neg': 0.183, 'neu': 0.709, 'pos': 0.108, 'compound': -0.25}",India
5,,"""Freedom will become the rule again and prohibition will be the exception,"" «The end of #confinement will allow us… ",domwabs,"Lyon, France",[],"{'neg': 0.0, 'neu': 0.736, 'pos': 0.264, 'compound': 0.7269}",France
6,,Two countries united efforts to kill the #CoronaVirus in between them.PS. Sharp weapons used ,Vas_Ah,"Jammu, Jammu And Kashmir","[('Two', 'CARDINAL'), ('CoronaVirus', 'PERSON')]","{'neg': 0.355, 'neu': 0.514, 'pos': 0.131, 'compound': -0.7003}",Jammu
7,, Keeping the spirit of generosity alive during #COVID19 pandemic. #relief programme at Thaiba Garden and near by villages.…,rafeek_rapi,,"[('Thaiba Garden', 'FAC')]","{'neg': 0.0, 'neu': 0.664, 'pos': 0.336, 'compound': 0.765}",
8,,"""Government rejected radical lockdown of England's care homes"" #coronavirus Is anyone surprised? This govt is so cl… ",buddah_uk,Not in Surrey,"[('England', 'GPE')]","{'neg': 0.147, 'neu': 0.625, 'pos': 0.228, 'compound': 0.2023}",Canada
9,, The smoking gun of govt care home policy?Govt advice from 2 April.“Some of these patients may have #COVOD19. All ca…,tonyevansace,,"[('2 April', 'DATE'), ('COVOD19', 'MONEY')]","{'neg': 0.106, 'neu': 0.752, 'pos': 0.142, 'compound': 0.2023}",
10,, Douche...it's been proven that the shutting down of places have decreased the spread of #coronavirus. Wit… ,HawaiianKeno,,"[('Douche', 'ORG')]","{'neg': 0.0, 'neu': 1.0, 'pos': 0.0, 'compound': 0.0}",
11,, It took  one day to issue an #ExecutiveOrder because he was upset Twitter called him out on his lies.I…,MelandTrevor33,EC,"[('one day', 'DATE'), ('ExecutiveOrder', 'MONEY')]","{'neg': 0.126, 'neu': 0.874, 'pos': 0.0, 'compound': -0.3818}",USA
12,, #Coronavirus has not stopped Modi-Shah's police to target Muslim students for participating in anti-citizenship act protest!!…,Khanafr00670701,,"[('Coronavirus', 'PERSON'), (""Modi-Shah's"", 'ORG'), ('Muslim', 'NORP')]","{'neg': 0.0, 'neu': 0.87, 'pos': 0.13, 'compound': 0.3071}",
13,," Vital emergency Govt funding has helped, but #LocalGov could need as much as £6bn more to cover the financial impact of #coro…",nickysarahlow1,"South East, England","[('Vital', 'ORG'), ('Govt', 'ORG'), ('LocalGov', 'PERSON'), ('as much as £6bn', 'MONEY')]","{'neg': 0.077, 'neu': 0.855, 'pos': 0.068, 'compound': -0.0516}",UK
14,," #Tokyo Tower celebrated its reopening Thursday with a colorful #illumination, wishing to be a “light of hope” for the c…",sakaki_chrono,"Minnesota, USA","[('Thursday', 'DATE')]","{'neg': 0.0, 'neu': 0.741, 'pos': 0.259, 'compound': 0.6808}",USA
15,," New data show almost 3,000 people who arrived in the airport between April 28 and May 21 did not say where they will be self-…",AntiQuango,,"[('almost 3,000', 'CARDINAL'), ('between April 28', 'DATE'), ('May 21', 'DATE')]","{'neg': 0.0, 'neu': 1.0, 'pos': 0.0, 'compound': 0.0}",
16,, A Corona patient fell in love with the doctor who treated him. He took two months after that both of them got engaged in th…,Olaf_Ke,,"[('two months', 'DATE')]","{'neg': 0.0, 'neu': 0.761, 'pos': 0.239, 'compound': 0.7845}",
17,, Wear a mask. You're protecting others #coronavirus,unipede,"Hougham, nr Grantham, England",[],"{'neg': 0.0, 'neu': 1.0, 'pos': 0.0, 'compound': 0.0}",UK
18,," #BREAKING: Hong Kong sees more than a dozen confirmed #coronavirus infection after two weeks of subsidence, multiple lo…",ignis_fatum,"Holon, Israel","[('Hong Kong', 'GPE'), ('more than a dozen', 'CARDINAL'), ('two weeks', 'DATE')]","{'neg': 0.0, 'neu': 1.0, 'pos': 0.0, 'compound': 0.0}",Israel
19,,I just cannot accept the reality of America let people to protest with automatic rifles against #Coronavirus lockdo… ,Borakmusik,"Los Angeles, CA","[('America', 'GPE'), ('Coronavirus', 'PERSON')]","{'neg': 0.218, 'neu': 0.782, 'pos': 0.0, 'compound': -0.4912}",USA
20,," As we are grieving the loss of 100,000 souls in America to the #coronavirus that has disproportionately impacted communitie…",CatLovington,,"[('100,000', 'CARDINAL'), ('America', 'GPE')]","{'neg': 0.248, 'neu': 0.752, 'pos': 0.0, 'compound': -0.6808}",
21,, 🇸🇦🇸🇦Pledging the support of  companies to our government &amp; country in the fight against #Coronavirus#WeA…,HIrfanKhan1,"Maharashtra, India","[('🇸🇦🇸', 'ORG'), ('Coronavirus#WeA', 'PERSON')]","{'neg': 0.142, 'neu': 0.71, 'pos': 0.148, 'compound': 0.0258}",India
22,, It took  one day to issue an #ExecutiveOrder because he was upset Twitter called him out on his lies.I…,kipfinch,"iPhone: 41.727821,-73.224327","[('one day', 'DATE'), ('ExecutiveOrder', 'MONEY')]","{'neg': 0.126, 'neu': 0.874, 'pos': 0.0, 'compound': -0.3818}",Error
23,, #Coronavirus has not stopped Modi-Shah's police to target Muslim students for participating in anti-citizenship act protest!!…,kotak_nimesh,"Kalyan, Maharashtra, INDIA","[('Coronavirus', 'PERSON'), (""Modi-Shah's"", 'ORG'), ('Muslim', 'NORP')]","{'neg': 0.0, 'neu': 0.87, 'pos': 0.13, 'compound': 0.3071}",India
24,," #Tokyo Tower celebrated its reopening Thursday with a colorful #illumination, wishing to be a “light of hope” for the c…",NoGrapCenation,💖🎺🌟スターちゃんの天国,"[('Thursday', 'DATE')]","{'neg': 0.0, 'neu': 0.741, 'pos': 0.259, 'compound': 0.6808}",Error
25,," #BREAKING: Hong Kong sees more than a dozen confirmed #coronavirus infection after two weeks of subsidence, multiple lo…",BCWildfireWkly,"British Columbia, Canada","[('Hong Kong', 'GPE'), ('more than a dozen', 'CARDINAL'), ('two weeks', 'DATE')]","{'neg': 0.0, 'neu': 1.0, 'pos': 0.0, 'compound': 0.0}",Canada
26,, Delhi HC Directs Delhi Govt To File Status Report In Suo Moto Matter Concerning Proper Disposal Of Bodies of  #COVID19 Vict…,help_delhi,,"[('Delhi', 'GPE'), ('Delhi Govt', 'ORG')]","{'neg': 0.0, 'neu': 0.948, 'pos': 0.052, 'compound': 0.0258}",
27,,"If we all #StayAlert and follow the guidance, we can control the virus.  You can find all the latest information re… ",StapleTye,"Staple Tye, Harlow","[('StayAlert', 'PERSON')]","{'neg': 0.0, 'neu': 1.0, 'pos': 0.0, 'compound': 0.0}",UK
28,, The smoking gun of govt care home policy?Govt advice from 2 April.“Some of these patients may have #COVOD19. All ca…,cutter78,warrington,"[('2 April', 'DATE'), ('COVOD19', 'MONEY')]","{'neg': 0.106, 'neu': 0.752, 'pos': 0.142, 'compound': 0.2023}",UK
29,,"Hi, if you'd like a copy of my little labour of love click on  and download for free ❤ .Than… ",Janethypnosis,"Dundonald, Northern Ireland",[],"{'neg': 0.0, 'neu': 0.606, 'pos': 0.394, 'compound': 0.8669}",UK
30,,Trending Now: ,,,,,
,,,,,,,
#Coronavirus | #Trump | #Police | #Minneapolis | #George | #Floyd | #Death | #After | #Protests |… ,TomPaineToday,My Country is the World.,"[('Coronavirus', 'PERSON'), ('Trump', 'PERSON'), ('Floyd', 'PERSON')]","{'neg': 0.0, 'neu': 1.0, 'pos': 0.0, 'compound': 0.0}",Error,,
31,," 100,000 American lives lost to #coronavirus. #100,000 grandparents, siblings, aunts, uncles, cousins. Coworkers, neigh…",Grace516G,VA-United States of America,"[('100,000', 'CARDINAL'), ('American', 'NORP'), ('100,000', 'MONEY')]","{'neg': 0.15, 'neu': 0.85, 'pos': 0.0, 'compound': -0.3182}",USA
32,,Key Action #3 for mitigating Cyber Security Risks associalted with remote working - Monitor for new threats that ma… ,SavantiUK,"London, England","[('Cyber Security Risks', 'PERSON')]","{'neg': 0.22, 'neu': 0.673, 'pos': 0.108, 'compound': -0.3612}",UK
33,,Explore the revival of linear broadcast TV amid the #coronavirus pandemic.  (via ) ,globalwebindex,London,[],"{'neg': 0.0, 'neu': 1.0, 'pos': 0.0, 'compound': 0.0}",UK
34,,#Coronavirus: Groups of six can meet in gardens as Boris Johnson announces lockdown changes,MetroRadioNews,North East of England,"[('Coronavirus', 'PERSON'), ('six', 'CARDINAL'), ('Boris Johnson', 'PERSON')]","{'neg': 0.0, 'neu': 1.0, 'pos': 0.0, 'compound': 0.0}",UK
35,,SCMP: #China pledges largest-ever economic rescue package to save jobs and livelihoods amid #coronavirusPremier Li… ,PM_Thornton,"Oxford, UK","[('China', 'GPE'), '', ('Li', 'PERSON')]","{'neg': 0.0, 'neu': 0.588, 'pos': 0.412, 'compound': 0.8126}",UK
36,,#Coronavirus: Groups of six can meet in gardens as Boris Johnson announces lockdown changes,TFMRadioNews,North East of England,"[('Coronavirus', 'PERSON'), ('six', 'CARDINAL'), ('Boris Johnson', 'PERSON')]","{'neg': 0.0, 'neu': 1.0, 'pos': 0.0, 'compound': 0.0}",UK
37,,Key Action #3 for mitigating Cyber Security Risks associalted with remote working - Monitor for new threats that ma… ,SavantiRussell,,"[('Cyber Security Risks', 'PERSON')]","{'neg': 0.22, 'neu': 0.673, 'pos': 0.108, 'compound': -0.3612}",
38,," Building in #Mudanjiang Welded As New Clusters Emerge Mudanjiang, a north-eastern Chinese city with 2.8million resident…",corona_china,,"[('Mudanjiang Welded', 'PERSON'), ('Emerge Mudanjiang', 'PERSON'), ('Chinese', 'NORP')]","{'neg': 0.0, 'neu': 1.0, 'pos': 0.0, 'compound': 0.0}",
39,,I always said 2020 was gonna be a movie... I wasn't thinking this kind of movie but #coronavirus #BlackLivesMater #Thugs,oliwontshutup1,,"[('2020', 'DATE'), '', '']","{'neg': 0.0, 'neu': 1.0, 'pos': 0.0, 'compound': 0.0}",
40,," India is fighting a war at multiple fronts against #coronavirus, Pakistan state sponsored terror, Chinese transgressions…",neelimatripathi,INDIA (Mumbai),"[('India', 'GPE'), ('coronavirus', 'MONEY'), ('Pakistan', 'GPE'), ('Chinese', 'NORP')]","{'neg': 0.45, 'neu': 0.55, 'pos': 0.0, 'compound': -0.8689}",India
41,, #AkshayKumar Extends His Support With A #NGO To Provide #SanitaryNapkins And #Kits To #DailyWageWorkers …,ItsBirendra_,A K K I W O O D,[],"{'neg': 0.0, 'neu': 0.724, 'pos': 0.276, 'compound': 0.4939}",Error
42,," ""The #Covid19 pandemic has resulted in the worst worker safety crisis in OSHA's 50-year history.”Democrat lawmakers accuse…",BBeshoar,"Longmont, CO","[('OSHA', 'ORG')]","{'neg': 0.328, 'neu': 0.56, 'pos': 0.112, 'compound': -0.7506}",USA
43,," While the world is busy fighting #CoronavirusPandemic, #Israel government led by corrupt #Netanyahu exploiting this to build…",basemn63,Gaza-Palestine,"[('CoronavirusPandemic', 'PERSON'), ('Israel', 'GPE'), ('Netanyahu', 'PERSON')]","{'neg': 0.265, 'neu': 0.735, 'pos': 0.0, 'compound': -0.6597}",Gaza Strip
44,,"India records largest single-day spike of 7,466 #Covid19 cases.  Read more #Coronavirus updates:… ",BloombergQuint,"Mumbai, India","[('India', 'GPE'), ('7,466 #Covid19', 'MONEY'), ('Read', 'ORG'), ('Coronavirus', 'PERSON')]","{'neg': 0.0, 'neu': 1.0, 'pos': 0.0, 'compound': 0.0}",India
45,," China now has five #vaccines, one vector and four inactivated, that have entered the first two phases of clinical trials in…",connecteddale,Cape Town,"[('China', 'GPE'), ('five', 'CARDINAL'), ('one', 'CARDINAL'), ('four', 'CARDINAL'), ('first', 'ORDINAL'), ('two', 'CARDINAL')]","{'neg': 0.0, 'neu': 1.0, 'pos': 0.0, 'compound': 0.0}",South Africa
46,, Delhi: Traffic congestion at Delhi-Gurugram border after Haryana government yesterday sealed borders with the national capital due…,Pal39534007,Mumbai Kanjurmarg West,"[('Delhi', 'GPE'), ('Delhi-Gurugram', 'ORG'), ('Haryana', 'GPE'), ('yesterday', 'DATE')]","{'neg': 0.0, 'neu': 1.0, 'pos': 0.0, 'compound': 0.0}",India
47,," Killing 101,000+ Americans by mismanaging the #coronavirus isn't enough, now  is threatening to just shoot Am…",PoliticalBee,Florida,"[('101,000', 'CARDINAL'), ('Americans', 'NORP')]","{'neg': 0.44, 'neu': 0.56, 'pos': 0.0, 'compound': -0.8807}",USA
48,,"Eleven #coronavirus patients have lost the battle for their lives and a total of 50 people recovered, health ministry added.#Afghanistan",TheKillidGroup,"Kabul, Afghanistan","[('50', 'CARDINAL')]","{'neg': 0.224, 'neu': 0.776, 'pos': 0.0, 'compound': -0.5994}",Afghanistan
49,, It took Trump at least two months to respond to the #coronavirus which resulted in the deaths of tens of thousands of Ameri…,BMPcharlotte,Planet Earth,"[('Trump', 'PERSON'), ('at least two months', 'DATE'), ('tens of thousands', 'CARDINAL')]","{'neg': 0.0, 'neu': 1.0, 'pos': 0.0, 'compound': 0.0}",USA
50,, We are now launching NHS Test and Trace to reduce the spread of #coronavirus and get life back to normal.This service will…,LBofHounslow,"Hounslow, west London","[('NHS Test and Trace', 'LAW')]","{'neg': 0.0, 'neu': 1.0, 'pos': 0.0, 'compound': 0.0}",UK
51,," Wearing a face mask has become an uncomfortable fact of life as Europeans leave lockdown. But for deaf people, it has become…",opslt79,,"[('Europeans', 'NORP')]","{'neg': 0.167, 'neu': 0.833, 'pos': 0.0, 'compound': -0.4215}",
52,, The role of steel in maintaining normal life in difficult times is key #DidYouKnow food packaged in steel cans has the…,APEAL_EU,Brussels,[],"{'neg': 0.111, 'neu': 0.889, 'pos': 0.0, 'compound': -0.3612}",Belgium
53,,Examine The Yourself....PC - SIS💗#photoshoot #nature #loveyourself #covid_19 #coronavirus #playtime #badminton🏸… ,Muthuhari43,"Tamilnadu,Erode,Gobi","['', '']","{'neg': 0.0, 'neu': 1.0, 'pos': 0.0, 'compound': 0.0}",India
54,,"The Time of Refreshment: Here is the 1st part to my phone sermon that I had earlier, and redid it on #youtube. Enjo… ",giantsfan5690,,"[('The Time of Refreshment', 'ORG'), ('1st', 'ORDINAL'), ('youtube', 'MONEY')]","{'neg': 0.0, 'neu': 1.0, 'pos': 0.0, 'compound': 0.0}",
55,," 🔥NEW EPISODE OF🔥 🔥🔥THE GUTTER🔥🔥 😷MASKED WARRIORS😷We talk plans for our new phone line, #riots &amp; SJWsLeave us a mes…",TheCaryM,Same contaminated rock as you,"[('GUTTER', 'ORG'), ('MASKED WARRIORS😷', 'FAC'), '']","{'neg': 0.0, 'neu': 1.0, 'pos': 0.0, 'compound': 0.0}",Error
56,, Want to “fire up the local economy” as we recover from the #coronavirus pandemic? “Research from  in 2018 found that…,ivana_vankova,,"['', ('2018', 'DATE')]","{'neg': 0.0, 'neu': 0.936, 'pos': 0.064, 'compound': 0.0772}",
57,,[CORONAVIRUS UPDATE] ADLSA stresses importance of adhering to precautionary measures after return of government sec… ,ILQLive,"Doha, Qatar","[('ADLSA', 'NORP')]","{'neg': 0.162, 'neu': 0.703, 'pos': 0.135, 'compound': -0.128}",Qatar
58,, How is the #coronavirus pandemic affecting museums worldwide?90% of them have closed their doors during the crisis and more t…,ENCATC,"Brussels, Belgium","[('worldwide?90%', 'PERCENT')]","{'neg': 0.177, 'neu': 0.823, 'pos': 0.0, 'compound': -0.6249}",Belgium
59,, Always remember that during a pandemic and tens of thousands of Brits dead that this was the Conservative Secretary Of…,IndyForTheGuy,Scotland,"[('tens of thousands', 'CARDINAL'), ('Brits', 'NORP'), ('Conservative', 'NORP')]","{'neg': 0.193, 'neu': 0.807, 'pos': 0.0, 'compound': -0.6486}",UK
60,, #Hackers are increasing attacks on #healthcare facilities and researchers during #CoronavirusPandemic #CyberSecurity #Coro…,FrRonconi,Padova,"[('Hackers', 'PERSON'), '', ('Coro', 'PERSON')]","{'neg': 0.195, 'neu': 0.805, 'pos': 0.0, 'compound': -0.4404}",Italy
61,, The PM blocking questions to Vallance and Whitty for their view on Cummings is completely wrong and the public will draw…,prthomas68,,"[('Vallance', 'GPE'), ('Cummings', 'ORG')]","{'neg': 0.24, 'neu': 0.76, 'pos': 0.0, 'compound': -0.7178}",
62,," Killing 101,000+ Americans by mismanaging the #coronavirus isn't enough, now  is threatening to just shoot Am…",raveninak,"Alaska, USA","[('101,000', 'CARDINAL'), ('Americans', 'NORP')]","{'neg': 0.44, 'neu': 0.56, 'pos': 0.0, 'compound': -0.8807}",USA
63,," Omg, this is a terribly damning indictment of this govt's handling of the #coronavirus crisis. The number of #COVID19 de…",Litter_Patrol,Blackburn,"[('Omg', 'PERSON'), '']","{'neg': 0.383, 'neu': 0.568, 'pos': 0.049, 'compound': -0.8689}",UK
64,," Tokyo confirms 22 new cases of the new #coronavirus today, reaching over 20 for the first time since May 14. I hope this is…",BBCOkinawa,"Okinawa-ken, Japan","[('Tokyo', 'GPE'), ('22', 'CARDINAL'), ('today', 'DATE'), ('over 20', 'CARDINAL'), ('first', 'ORDINAL'), ('May 14', 'DATE')]","{'neg': 0.0, 'neu': 0.817, 'pos': 0.183, 'compound': 0.5719}",Japan
65,,#COVID19  has forced #Canadians to start having the difficult conversation about managing #household #debt.🍁💸… ,silberschmelzer,,"[('Canadians', 'NORP'), '']","{'neg': 0.314, 'neu': 0.686, 'pos': 0.0, 'compound': -0.6705}",
66,, Trump &amp; the GOP have turned the US into a shit-hole countryA White Supremacist in the W.H Racism &amp; murder is rifeRu…,Imatq1,"Napa, CA","[('Trump &amp', 'ORG'), ('GOP', 'ORG'), ('US', 'GPE'), ('countryA', 'ORG'), ('White Supremacist', 'ORG'), ('the W.H Racism &amp', 'ORG'), ('rifeRu', 'CARDINAL')]","{'neg': 0.311, 'neu': 0.636, 'pos': 0.053, 'compound': -0.8519}",USA
67,, Thanks for the update. But will Twitter be fact checking Communist China’s lies about the #coronavirus? What about Chin…,rottaerkki,,"[('Communist', 'NORP'), ('China', 'GPE'), ('Chin', 'PERSON')]","{'neg': 0.123, 'neu': 0.749, 'pos': 0.128, 'compound': 0.0258}",
68,," There's still no vaccine against #Coronavirus. So, it becomes imperative to pray to Almighty, to boost your own willpowe…",MeetSinghinsan1,,"[('Coronavirus', 'PERSON')]","{'neg': 0.095, 'neu': 0.69, 'pos': 0.216, 'compound': 0.4215}",
69,," As we are grieving the loss of 100,000 souls in America to the #coronavirus that has disproportionately impacted communitie…",nadinemarissa,"Los Angeles,CA","[('100,000', 'CARDINAL'), ('America', 'GPE')]","{'neg': 0.248, 'neu': 0.752, 'pos': 0.0, 'compound': -0.6808}",USA
70,," California sitting at 2,817 new COVID cases. A new single day record. Godspeed. I’m staying inside. #coronaVirus #covid19",gilbertstudioz,Sugar Cane,"[('California', 'GPE'), ('2,817', 'CARDINAL'), ('COVID', 'ORG'), '']","{'neg': 0.0, 'neu': 1.0, 'pos': 0.0, 'compound': 0.0}",USA
71,, The European #banking sector could take four years to return to pre-#coronavirus levels. ,DLDConference,"Munich, Germany","[('European', 'NORP'), ('four years', 'DATE')]","{'neg': 0.0, 'neu': 1.0, 'pos': 0.0, 'compound': 0.0}",Germany
72,,As questions continue to be asked as to why #BorisJohnson govt. did NOT impose airport #quarantine &amp; #coronavirus c… ,CharterhouseSq,,"[('BorisJohnson', 'PERSON'), '']","{'neg': 0.0, 'neu': 0.905, 'pos': 0.095, 'compound': 0.2235}",
73,, Deteriorating government #institutions cost lives!Countries with the biggest decline in #government efficiency over th…,frankgcrowley,"Cork, Ireland","[('lives!Countries', 'GPE')]","{'neg': 0.0, 'neu': 0.823, 'pos': 0.177, 'compound': 0.4199}",Ireland
74,, Learn how cash transfers are helping those worst affected by #Coronavirus in #Pakistan. Schemes like this are helping c…,saimasyed01,London,"[('Coronavirus', 'PERSON'), ('Pakistan', 'GPE')]","{'neg': 0.214, 'neu': 0.526, 'pos': 0.259, 'compound': 0.0516}",UK
75,,Strong fall in #Producer #Prices in industry in April 2020 (–2.3%) -  #Agenparl #Coronavirus… ,Agenparl,Roma,"[('April 2020', 'DATE'), ('2.3%', 'PERCENT'), ('Coronavirus', 'PERSON')]","{'neg': 0.0, 'neu': 0.784, 'pos': 0.216, 'compound': 0.5106}",Montgomery County
76,," As we are grieving the loss of 100,000 souls in America to the #coronavirus that has disproportionately impacted communitie…",Siadasha,Deutschland,"[('100,000', 'CARDINAL'), ('America', 'GPE')]","{'neg': 0.248, 'neu': 0.752, 'pos': 0.0, 'compound': -0.6808}",Germany
77,,How often do you keep in touch with friends and family👨‍👩‍👦‍👦..??Share your #Opinion daily by following us… ,RoutesGray,"Mumbai, India","[('Opinion', 'PERSON'), ('daily', 'DATE')]","{'neg': 0.0, 'neu': 0.822, 'pos': 0.178, 'compound': 0.5362}",India
78,,"Where's that graph gone that the government kept rolling out,showing the death rate in our country compared to othe… ",cumston_gary,Stockport,[],"{'neg': 0.178, 'neu': 0.822, 'pos': 0.0, 'compound': -0.5994}",UK
79,," . is this true👇?If yes,do you have an alternative plan in place?Are #ventilators, scarce?If #ICUs are runn…",VijayShenli,,[],"{'neg': 0.0, 'neu': 1.0, 'pos': 0.0, 'compound': 0.0}",
80,, Wow! Look at these numbers! Can’t wait to hear Dr. Fauci and the CDC explain why it is that #coronavirus preferred to str…,NjPsalms91,,"[('Fauci', 'PERSON'), ('CDC', 'ORG'), ('coronavirus', 'PERSON'), ('str', 'ORG')]","{'neg': 0.0, 'neu': 0.834, 'pos': 0.166, 'compound': 0.658}",
81,," Really appreciate the courage of our #CovidWarriors like Sarpanch, Anganwadi &amp; ASHA workers who have showed commitment…",SurathBehera9,,"[('Sarpanch, Anganwadi &amp', 'ORG')]","{'neg': 0.0, 'neu': 0.61, 'pos': 0.39, 'compound': 0.8384}",
82,, #Thailand - Curfew shortened from 11pm to 3am - Shopping malls to close at 9pm (previously 8pm) - Beauty clinics &amp; massage p…,Ethan_mcu,ประเทศไทย,"[('Thailand - Curfew', 'ORG'), ('11', 'CARDINAL'), ('3am', 'QUANTITY'), ('9', 'CARDINAL'), ('8', 'CARDINAL')]","{'neg': 0.0, 'neu': 0.833, 'pos': 0.167, 'compound': 0.5859}",Thailand
83,, It took  one day to issue an #ExecutiveOrder because he was upset Twitter called him out on his lies.I…,mwood4494,,"[('one day', 'DATE'), ('ExecutiveOrder', 'MONEY')]","{'neg': 0.126, 'neu': 0.874, 'pos': 0.0, 'compound': -0.3818}",
84,,"The US would announce 'certain decisions' on #China today, said President #DonaldTrump as he emphasised that Beijin… ",moneycontrolcom,Mumbai,"[('US', 'GPE'), ('China', 'GPE'), ('today', 'DATE'), ('DonaldTrump', 'PERSON'), ('Beijin', 'ORG')]","{'neg': 0.0, 'neu': 0.884, 'pos': 0.116, 'compound': 0.2732}",India
85,,#ClevelandClinic researchers studying if #stemcells could help treat ARDS in #coronavirus patients ,ShivaniIVF,India,"[('ClevelandClinic', 'ORG')]","{'neg': 0.0, 'neu': 0.649, 'pos': 0.351, 'compound': 0.6597}",India
86,," But you stood back and let 100,000 Americans die from #COVID19 #coronavirus #BlackLivesMatter",Vices_Virtues,"Orange, New Jersey","[('100,000', 'CARDINAL'), ('Americans', 'NORP'), '']","{'neg': 0.245, 'neu': 0.755, 'pos': 0.0, 'compound': -0.5994}",USA
87,," Latest update on #COVID19 in #Odisha: As on midnight, 27th May, 139311 samples have been tested &amp; 1660 cases have been teste…",Debasish_John,"Cuttack, India","[('Odisha', 'PERSON'), ('midnight', 'TIME'), ('May, 139311', 'DATE'), ('1660', 'DATE')]","{'neg': 0.0, 'neu': 1.0, 'pos': 0.0, 'compound': 0.0}",India
88,,Me at the year 2020 #BlackLivesMatters #coronavirus ,DelenaMisaMSR,"Fort Saskatchewan, Alberta","[('the year', 'DATE'), '']","{'neg': 0.0, 'neu': 1.0, 'pos': 0.0, 'compound': 0.0}",Canada
89,, The below visualization The Secret History of #Coronavirus is based on GreatGameIndia‘s exclusive report Coronavirus Bi…,GreatGameIndia,India,"[('The Secret History', 'WORK_OF_ART'), ('Coronavirus', 'PERSON'), ('GreatGameIndia‘s', 'ORG'), ('Coronavirus Bi', 'PERSON')]","{'neg': 0.0, 'neu': 0.909, 'pos': 0.091, 'compound': 0.128}",India
90,, 🇨🇳 #China pledges largest-ever economic rescue package to save jobs and livelihoods amid #coronavirus - SCMP*Li Keqiang con…,FdcCapital,"Paris, France","[('China', 'GPE')]","{'neg': 0.0, 'neu': 0.625, 'pos': 0.375, 'compound': 0.8126}",France
91,," As we are grieving the loss of 100,000 souls in America to the #coronavirus that has disproportionately impacted communitie…",bndsnoopy61,MI,"[('100,000', 'CARDINAL'), ('America', 'GPE')]","{'neg': 0.248, 'neu': 0.752, 'pos': 0.0, 'compound': -0.6808}",USA
92,," ""The mortality [rate] in our hospital is very, very high.""Cemeteries are overflowing in Yemen as #coronavirus-related deat…",ASH2030ASH,Riyadh,"[('Yemen', 'GPE')]","{'neg': 0.0, 'neu': 1.0, 'pos': 0.0, 'compound': 0.0}",Riyadh Saudi Arabia
93,, So VC UHS  is ready to die while treating patients (God forbid) but what if we don't want to risk our and ou…,MaarwaMajical,,[],"{'neg': 0.141, 'neu': 0.71, 'pos': 0.148, 'compound': 0.0485}",
94,,#Coronavirus: What is #hydroxychloroquine and why is New Zealand throwing money at it?  … ,Video_Forensics,,"[('Coronavirus', 'PERSON'), ('New Zealand', 'GPE')]","{'neg': 0.0, 'neu': 1.0, 'pos': 0.0, 'compound': 0.0}",
95,," Talk about making work for yourself.. In March Baroness Dido Harding part of Board of Jockey Club which ""courageously"" d…",lexingtonia,,"[('March', 'DATE'), ('Dido Harding', 'PERSON'), ('Board of Jockey Club', 'ORG')]","{'neg': 0.0, 'neu': 1.0, 'pos': 0.0, 'compound': 0.0}",
96,," #coronavirus update in #ElSalvador. New recovered 13, new deaths 3. Total cases in El Salvador confirmed 2194, recovered…",AmandaCamposSv,,"[('ElSalvador', 'PERSON'), ('13', 'CARDINAL'), ('3', 'CARDINAL'), ('El Salvador', 'GPE'), ('2194', 'DATE')]","{'neg': 0.0, 'neu': 1.0, 'pos': 0.0, 'compound': 0.0}",
97,, #AugmentedReality with  to let doctors to connect with colleagues across Earth#RemoteWork #XR #COVID19 #Co…,FrRonconi,Padova,[],"{'neg': 0.0, 'neu': 1.0, 'pos': 0.0, 'compound': 0.0}",Italy
98,,"#Schools will reopen on Monday, prime minister Boris Johnson has confirmed yesterday afternoon &gt;&gt; All the latest fr… ",GKPComms,"London, England","[('Schools', 'PERSON'), ('Monday', 'DATE'), ('Boris Johnson', 'PERSON'), ('yesterday', 'DATE'), ('afternoon', 'TIME')]","{'neg': 0.0, 'neu': 1.0, 'pos': 0.0, 'compound': 0.0}",UK
99,, We have manufactured a #covid19 Rapid Test Kit that will show whether u have been exposed to &amp; or have built up antibodie…,UltiMeGa,"California, USA","[('Rapid Test Kit', 'PERSON')]","{'neg': 0.061, 'neu': 0.939, 'pos': 0.0, 'compound': -0.0772}",USA
100,,460 new cases and 7 new deaths in Armenia [8:04 GMT] #coronavirus #CoronaVirusUpdate #COVID19 #CoronavirusPandemic,COVIDLive,,"[('460', 'CARDINAL'), ('7', 'CARDINAL'), ('Armenia', 'GPE'), ('8:04', 'TIME'), '', '']","{'neg': 0.0, 'neu': 1.0, 'pos': 0.0, 'compound': 0.0}",
101,,Delhi HC Directs Delhi Govt To File Status Report In Suo Moto Matter Concerning Proper Disposal Of Bodies of… ,gulshanNBT,New Delhi,"[('Delhi', 'GPE'), ('Delhi Govt', 'ORG')]","{'neg': 0.0, 'neu': 0.942, 'pos': 0.058, 'compound': 0.0258}",India
102,,The #coronavirus pandemic should change the way we look at #national #security. ,carlesdijous,"Barcelona, Catalonia","['', '']","{'neg': 0.0, 'neu': 1.0, 'pos': 0.0, 'compound': 0.0}",Spain
103,, This piece is about the lack of public mourning for so many US deaths from #coronavirus.  Public mourning not welcomed by d…,shawnsharif,Thailand,"[('US', 'GPE')]","{'neg': 0.36, 'neu': 0.64, 'pos': 0.0, 'compound': -0.8456}",Thailand
104,," #CellularandMolecularBiology (CCMB) on Thursday announced that it has established a stable culture of #coronavirus, which wil…",1995MODASSIR,"nim.Tamluk,purba mednipur(W.B)","[('Thursday', 'DATE')]","{'neg': 0.0, 'neu': 0.864, 'pos': 0.136, 'compound': 0.296}",India
105,," #Tokyo Tower celebrated its reopening Thursday with a colorful #illumination, wishing to be a “light of hope” for the c…",BlasterYuki,"Hawaii, United States","[('Thursday', 'DATE')]","{'neg': 0.0, 'neu': 0.741, 'pos': 0.259, 'compound': 0.6808}",USA
106,,Don't tell me a #government minister has been caught lying to us plebs again. Hard to believe not.#BuryStEdmunds… ,Suffolkbeeman,"West Suffolk, UK",[],"{'neg': 0.242, 'neu': 0.758, 'pos': 0.0, 'compound': -0.5859}",UK
107,, The number of Americans who have lost their jobs in the past 10 weeks soared to more than 40 million.1 in 4 American wo…,fiona_fionnagal,Angus,"[('Americans', 'NORP'), ('the past 10 weeks', 'DATE'), ('more than 40', 'CARDINAL'), ('4', 'CARDINAL'), ('American', 'NORP')]","{'neg': 0.093, 'neu': 0.854, 'pos': 0.053, 'compound': -0.25}",USA
108,," #Covid19: Highest spike of 7,466 fresh cases &amp; 175 related deaths reported in the last 24 hours | #Coronavirus #Live #Up…",Jasjitkamboj,"Mohali, India","[('7,466', 'CARDINAL'), ('175', 'CARDINAL'), ('the last 24 hours', 'TIME'), '', '']","{'neg': 0.0, 'neu': 0.892, 'pos': 0.108, 'compound': 0.3182}",India
109,, With 56.7 percents recovery rate against 16.38 percents of all India rate of #coronavirus cases Haryana is moving fast…,AjayLalawas,,"[('56.7', 'CARDINAL'), ('16.38', 'CARDINAL'), ('India', 'GPE'), '', ('Haryana', 'GPE')]","{'neg': 0.0, 'neu': 1.0, 'pos': 0.0, 'compound': 0.0}",
110,," #Coronavirus: #Diabetes leads to 1 in 10 dying in hospital within 7 days, finds study …",saramichael_f,"Manila, Philippines ","[('Coronavirus', 'PERSON'), ('Diabetes', 'PERSON'), ('1', 'CARDINAL'), ('10', 'CARDINAL'), ('7 days', 'DATE')]","{'neg': 0.0, 'neu': 1.0, 'pos': 0.0, 'compound': 0.0}",Philippines
111,," Comparison of #coronavirus  infection, recovery and testing rates internationally.#StayAtHomeSaveLives …",jbwhitesnake,scotland,"[('Comparison', 'PERSON')]","{'neg': 0.0, 'neu': 1.0, 'pos': 0.0, 'compound': 0.0}",UK
112,, #Coronavirus has not stopped Modi-Shah's police to target Muslim students for participating in anti-citizenship act protest!!…,anti_illumin4ti,,"[('Coronavirus', 'PERSON'), (""Modi-Shah's"", 'ORG'), ('Muslim', 'NORP')]","{'neg': 0.0, 'neu': 0.87, 'pos': 0.13, 'compound': 0.3071}",
113,, We have manufactured a #covid19 Rapid Test Kit that will show whether u have been exposed to &amp; or have built up antibod…,UltiMeGa,"California, USA","[('Rapid Test Kit', 'PERSON')]","{'neg': 0.061, 'neu': 0.939, 'pos': 0.0, 'compound': -0.0772}",USA
114,, BORIS TRUMP BOLSONARO JOHNSON Bitte lesen:    …,squashypigeon,"London, Europe.",[],"{'neg': 0.0, 'neu': 1.0, 'pos': 0.0, 'compound': 0.0}",UK
115,, A radical11-point plan to save lives proposing “a further lockdown of care homes” was submitted to Downing St on 28 Apr…,mediate4ueu,Scotland Eire Australia World,"[('Downing St', 'ORG'), ('28', 'CARDINAL')]","{'neg': 0.0, 'neu': 0.738, 'pos': 0.262, 'compound': 0.7506}",UK
116,," Journalists asking Vallance and Whitty for their view on Cummings matter. PM intervenes and stops them from answering, sa…",JJoyMatthews,"Darley Dale, Derbyshire","[('Vallance', 'ORG'), ('Cummings', 'ORG')]","{'neg': 0.081, 'neu': 0.863, 'pos': 0.056, 'compound': -0.128}",UK
117,, Key elements of Scotland’s test and protect #coronavirus contact tracing system explained in less than 30 seconds by ⁦…,Donaghmore36,,"[('Scotland', 'GPE'), ('less than 30 seconds', 'TIME')]","{'neg': 0.0, 'neu': 0.874, 'pos': 0.126, 'compound': 0.3818}",
118,, A radical11-point plan to save lives proposing “a further lockdown of care homes” was submitted to Downing St on 28 Apr…,eddietheknife,,"[('Downing St', 'ORG'), ('28', 'CARDINAL')]","{'neg': 0.0, 'neu': 0.738, 'pos': 0.262, 'compound': 0.7506}",
119,,"#Sweden and #EU: #Competitionlaw, #publicprocurement, and #stateaid in the wake of #COVID19#coronavirus",GComplianceNews,Global,"[('Sweden', 'PERSON'), ('EU', 'ORG'), ('Competitionlaw', 'PERSON')]","{'neg': 0.0, 'neu': 1.0, 'pos': 0.0, 'compound': 0.0}",USA
120,,💩💩💩 Why has Donald Trump acted 1000 times quicker and way more effectively on his pathetic little spat with… ,Paul_B_123,"East Midlands, England","[('Donald Trump', 'PERSON'), ('1000', 'CARDINAL')]","{'neg': 0.155, 'neu': 0.712, 'pos': 0.134, 'compound': -0.1298}",Error
121,," This week, Jewish leaders from across the globe discussed the needs of communities in a post-#coronavirus world.…",dyfededwards,"Whitstable, Caint, Lloegr","[('This week', 'DATE'), ('Jewish', 'NORP')]","{'neg': 0.0, 'neu': 1.0, 'pos': 0.0, 'compound': 0.0}",UK
122,, #ISIS is criticizing senior Muslim scholars for closing mosques as a preventative measure against the spread of the #cor…,thanveer_kamal,"New Delhi,India","[('ISIS', 'PERSON'), ('Muslim', 'NORP')]","{'neg': 0.128, 'neu': 0.872, 'pos': 0.0, 'compound': -0.3612}",India
123,, #Coronavirus has not stopped Modi-Shah's police to target Muslim students for participating in anti-citizenship act protest!!…,Bajpaipg,,"[('Coronavirus', 'PERSON'), (""Modi-Shah's"", 'ORG'), ('Muslim', 'NORP')]","{'neg': 0.0, 'neu': 0.87, 'pos': 0.13, 'compound': 0.3071}",
124,," Hey  Donny boy, between 100,000 dead #coronavirus victims, #MinneapolisUprising burning down a city, an…",Kenlenkirk,"Edmonton, Alberta","[('Donny', 'PERSON'), ('between 100,000', 'CARDINAL'), ('MinneapolisUprising', 'PERSON')]","{'neg': 0.375, 'neu': 0.625, 'pos': 0.0, 'compound': -0.765}",Canada
125,, The World Is Still Far From Herd Immunity for #CoronavirusUK ~7% seroprevalence but with ~38K de…,piminu,Madrid & London,"[('The World Is Still Far From Herd Immunity', 'ORG'), ('~38K de…', 'PERSON')]","{'neg': 0.0, 'neu': 1.0, 'pos': 0.0, 'compound': 0.0}",Spain
126,, #Coronavirus has not stopped Modi-Shah's police to target Muslim students for participating in anti-citizenship act protest!!…,REBEL86922635,Indian Occupied Kashmir,"[('Coronavirus', 'PERSON'), (""Modi-Shah's"", 'ORG'), ('Muslim', 'NORP')]","{'neg': 0.0, 'neu': 0.87, 'pos': 0.13, 'compound': 0.3071}",Jammu and Kashmir
127,," Journalists asking Vallance and Whitty for their view on Cummings matter. PM intervenes and stops them from answering, sa…",IsfreeJane,,"[('Vallance', 'ORG'), ('Cummings', 'ORG')]","{'neg': 0.081, 'neu': 0.863, 'pos': 0.056, 'compound': -0.128}",
128,, Thanks for the update. But will Twitter be fact checking Communist China’s lies about the #coronavirus? What about Chin…,Snikk,"New York, NY","[('Communist', 'NORP'), ('China', 'GPE'), ('Chin', 'PERSON')]","{'neg': 0.123, 'neu': 0.749, 'pos': 0.128, 'compound': 0.0258}",USA
129,," 100,000 dead AmericansAn innocent black man murdered in Minnesota by powers of authorityAnd our… ",ILikeTheFerns,Poland,"[('100,000', 'CARDINAL'), ('Minnesota', 'GPE'), ('authorityAnd', 'WORK_OF_ART')]","{'neg': 0.394, 'neu': 0.498, 'pos': 0.109, 'compound': -0.8074}",Poland
130,, #Coronavirus has not stopped Modi-Shah's police to target Muslim students for participating in anti-citizenship act protest!!…,msaadulhaq,Pakistan,"[('Coronavirus', 'PERSON'), (""Modi-Shah's"", 'ORG'), ('Muslim', 'NORP')]","{'neg': 0.0, 'neu': 0.87, 'pos': 0.13, 'compound': 0.3071}",Pakistan
131,, Self-employed? Find out about the range of support &amp; advice that’s available if your business has been affected by coronaviru…,DeborahOktar,171 York Road Belfast,"[('support &amp', 'ORG'), ('coronaviru', 'PERSON')]","{'neg': 0.072, 'neu': 0.807, 'pos': 0.121, 'compound': 0.2732}",UK
132,," 7,466 #coronavirus cases in India in 24 hours, biggest jump so far  ",rb6475,,"[('7,466 #coronavirus', 'MONEY'), ('India', 'GPE'), ('24 hours', 'TIME')]","{'neg': 0.0, 'neu': 1.0, 'pos': 0.0, 'compound': 0.0}",
133,, Let’s follow the lockdown guidelines and rules to be safe from #coronavirus. All stay at home unless absolutely necessar…,pradeepsinghneg,"Uttaranchal, India","[('coronavirus', 'PERSON')]","{'neg': 0.0, 'neu': 0.861, 'pos': 0.139, 'compound': 0.4404}",India
134,,"How the world’s most powerful country is handling covid-19? Contrary to what many Americans think, the death rate i… ",DocWissam,Belgique,"[('Americans', 'NORP')]","{'neg': 0.163, 'neu': 0.709, 'pos': 0.129, 'compound': -0.204}",Belgium
135,, #India emerging as new hotspot of #CoronavirusPandemic with record jumps in new cases in recent days …,GeromanAT,Milky Way,"[('India', 'GPE'), ('CoronavirusPandemic', 'PERSON'), ('recent days', 'DATE')]","{'neg': 0.0, 'neu': 1.0, 'pos': 0.0, 'compound': 0.0}",USA
136,, Thanks for the update. But will Twitter be fact checking Communist China’s lies about the #coronavirus? What about Chin…,rn_gal,Texas,"[('Communist', 'NORP'), ('China', 'GPE'), ('Chin', 'PERSON')]","{'neg': 0.123, 'neu': 0.749, 'pos': 0.128, 'compound': 0.0258}",USA
137,," Vital emergency Govt funding has helped, but #LocalGov could need as much as £6bn more to cover the financial impact of #coro…",AngelaHemingwa5,,"[('Vital', 'ORG'), ('Govt', 'ORG'), ('LocalGov', 'PERSON'), ('as much as £6bn', 'MONEY')]","{'neg': 0.077, 'neu': 0.855, 'pos': 0.068, 'compound': -0.0516}",
138,,"Italians found their way to pass-time during lockdown forced by #coronavirus, though it can be highly dangerous.… ",TomthunkitsMind,"Atlanta, GA","[('Italians', 'NORP'), ('coronavirus', 'PERSON')]","{'neg': 0.158, 'neu': 0.842, 'pos': 0.0, 'compound': -0.4588}",USA
139,," #BREAKING: Hong Kong sees more than a dozen confirmed #coronavirus infection after two weeks of subsidence, multiple lo…",guerradelsxxi,España,"[('Hong Kong', 'GPE'), ('more than a dozen', 'CARDINAL'), ('two weeks', 'DATE')]","{'neg': 0.0, 'neu': 1.0, 'pos': 0.0, 'compound': 0.0}",Spain
140,, Hospital workers kept in the dark about colleagues' coronavirus tests   #coronavirus…,jokbristol,Bristol,[],"{'neg': 0.0, 'neu': 1.0, 'pos': 0.0, 'compound': 0.0}",USA
141,," #BREAKING: Hong Kong sees more than a dozen confirmed #coronavirus infection after two weeks of subsidence, multiple lo…",niccijsmith,"Taipei City, Taiwan","[('Hong Kong', 'GPE'), ('more than a dozen', 'CARDINAL'), ('two weeks', 'DATE')]","{'neg': 0.0, 'neu': 1.0, 'pos': 0.0, 'compound': 0.0}",Taiwan
142,, COVID-19 AND GLOBAL WARMING: TWO GOOD REASONS TO EAT FEWER ANIMALS 🌎 🌳 🐂 🦇My new article on openDemocracy | Transform…,Giulia_Minoia,,"[('GLOBAL', 'ORG'), ('TWO', 'CARDINAL')]","{'neg': 0.0, 'neu': 0.715, 'pos': 0.285, 'compound': 0.7154}",
143,," In last 24 hours, 116 police personnel have tested positive for #Coronavirus in Maharashtra and 3 personnel have died due to the v…",bhangrepravin,mumbai,"[('last 24 hours', 'TIME'), ('116', 'CARDINAL'), ('Coronavirus', 'PERSON'), ('Maharashtra', 'ORG'), ('3', 'CARDINAL')]","{'neg': 0.132, 'neu': 0.735, 'pos': 0.132, 'compound': 0.0}",India
144,," Spent Eid morning with our unsung heroes at Field Hospital, RWP sports complex. #COVIDー19 patients in #Quarantine given…",TheMapleForce,Here,"[('Eid morning', 'TIME'), ('Field Hospital', 'FAC'), ('Quarantine', 'PERSON')]","{'neg': 0.0, 'neu': 0.837, 'pos': 0.163, 'compound': 0.5106}",Error
145,, Promote and market your youtube channel to increase subscribers #Allah_Not_Allowed_EatMeat #COVID…,jdkdoobbb,,"['', ('COVID', 'PERSON')]","{'neg': 0.0, 'neu': 0.647, 'pos': 0.353, 'compound': 0.5994}",
146,," As we are grieving the loss of 100,000 souls in America to the #coronavirus that has disproportionately impacted communitie…",CORCOVADOINVEST,,"[('100,000', 'CARDINAL'), ('America', 'GPE')]","{'neg': 0.248, 'neu': 0.752, 'pos': 0.0, 'compound': -0.6808}",
147,, Delhi: Traffic congestion at Delhi-Gurugram border after Haryana government yesterday sealed borders with the national capital due…,vibrantvivek_,India,"[('Delhi', 'GPE'), ('Delhi-Gurugram', 'ORG'), ('Haryana', 'GPE'), ('yesterday', 'DATE')]","{'neg': 0.0, 'neu': 1.0, 'pos': 0.0, 'compound': 0.0}",India
148,, Oh no. Spike in infections beginning in London. #COVID19 #coronavirus #NHS,ClareDodwell,,"[('London', 'GPE')]","{'neg': 0.18, 'neu': 0.82, 'pos': 0.0, 'compound': -0.296}",
149,, The boom in Latam/Sth Asia #coronavirus cases fits with the high positive % of tests recently. Record new cases on 28 May i…,MihrThakar,"Mombasa, Kenya","[('Latam/Sth', 'ORG'), ('28', 'CARDINAL')]","{'neg': 0.0, 'neu': 0.854, 'pos': 0.146, 'compound': 0.5574}",Kenya
150,, Secretary Social Welfare Punjab Zahid Saleem accompanied by  visited Union Council Morgah. Discussed taking all…,TheMapleForce,Here,"[('Social Welfare', 'PERSON'), ('Punjab Zahid Saleem', 'PERSON'), ('Union Council Morgah', 'ORG')]","{'neg': 0.0, 'neu': 1.0, 'pos': 0.0, 'compound': 0.0}",Error
151,,"#Health_Ministry: At least 623 cases of #coronavirus were recorded in the last 24 hours, bringing the total number… ",TheKillidGroup,"Kabul, Afghanistan","[('Health_Ministry', 'PERSON'), ('At least 623', 'CARDINAL'), ('the last 24 hours', 'TIME')]","{'neg': 0.0, 'neu': 1.0, 'pos': 0.0, 'compound': 0.0}",Afghanistan
152,,This  is why  the best case for the whole world and the humanity is that China or Cuba makes the vaccine first.… ,EuroPleasureMac,The State ,"[('China', 'GPE'), ('Cuba', 'GPE'), ('first', 'ORDINAL')]","{'neg': 0.0, 'neu': 0.833, 'pos': 0.167, 'compound': 0.6369}",United States
153,, Delhi: Traffic congestion at Delhi-Gurugram border after Haryana government yesterday sealed borders with the national capital due…,Deathstroke_IND,,"[('Delhi', 'GPE'), ('Delhi-Gurugram', 'ORG'), ('Haryana', 'GPE'), ('yesterday', 'DATE')]","{'neg': 0.0, 'neu': 1.0, 'pos': 0.0, 'compound': 0.0}",
154,,"But you stood back and let 100,000 Americans die from #COVID19 #coronavirus #BlackLivesMatter ",creolecanadian,Quarantined ,"[('100,000', 'CARDINAL'), ('Americans', 'NORP'), '']","{'neg': 0.245, 'neu': 0.755, 'pos': 0.0, 'compound': -0.5994}",Error
155,, #Dementia Gene Doubles Risk Of Becoming Severely Ill With #Coronavirus  via  #Alzheim…,_atanas_,,"[('Dementia Gene', 'PERSON'), ('Coronavirus', 'PERSON'), ('Alzheim', 'PERSON')]","{'neg': 0.467, 'neu': 0.533, 'pos': 0.0, 'compound': -0.7845}",
156,, This is the single biggest opportunity i've seen in a life time to build an average fortune fast. i urge every one to c…,NaattuVarthakal,കേരളം,[],"{'neg': 0.0, 'neu': 0.882, 'pos': 0.118, 'compound': 0.4215}",India
157,," Two friends banned today by a security guard from walking in an (otherwise empty) Thurston Gardens: “Sorry ma’am, #coron…",hockeyloversim,Fiji,"[('Two', 'CARDINAL'), ('today', 'DATE'), ('Thurston Gardens', 'FAC'), ('Sorry ma’am', 'WORK_OF_ART')]","{'neg': 0.128, 'neu': 0.638, 'pos': 0.234, 'compound': 0.3612}",Fiji
158,, This is the single biggest opportunity i've seen in a life time to build an average fortune fast. i urge every one to c…,ice_faki,,[],"{'neg': 0.0, 'neu': 0.882, 'pos': 0.118, 'compound': 0.4215}",
159,, #Coronavirus has not stopped Modi-Shah's police to target Muslim students for participating in anti-citizenship act protest!!…,makGauBalak,गौऊ शाला इन भक्तलैंड ,"[('Coronavirus', 'PERSON'), (""Modi-Shah's"", 'ORG'), ('Muslim', 'NORP')]","{'neg': 0.0, 'neu': 0.87, 'pos': 0.13, 'compound': 0.3071}",Error
160,, It took  one day to issue an #ExecutiveOrder because he was upset Twitter called him out on his lies.I…,Bruton65Paula,"Corsicana, TX","[('one day', 'DATE'), ('ExecutiveOrder', 'MONEY')]","{'neg': 0.126, 'neu': 0.874, 'pos': 0.0, 'compound': -0.3818}",USA
161,," 2020 is one of the worst years I have seen in my life.#CoronaVirus, #AmphanCyclone, #UttarakhandForestFire &amp; people dyin…",MalayaR79071541,,"[('2020', 'DATE'), ('one', 'CARDINAL'), ('the worst years', 'DATE')]","{'neg': 0.204, 'neu': 0.796, 'pos': 0.0, 'compound': -0.6249}",
162,, It took  one day to issue an #ExecutiveOrder because he was upset Twitter called him out on his lies.I…,HarmoniousLivn,UK,"[('one day', 'DATE'), ('ExecutiveOrder', 'MONEY')]","{'neg': 0.126, 'neu': 0.874, 'pos': 0.0, 'compound': -0.3818}",United Kingdom
163,,New photos show extent of ruin at Strathmartine Hospital as plans labelled last chance to save site… ,corona_scotnews,,"[('Strathmartine Hospital', 'ORG')]","{'neg': 0.165, 'neu': 0.609, 'pos': 0.226, 'compound': 0.1027}",
164,,29 May | International Day of  PeacekeepersWe applaud #womeninpeacekeeping working to curb the #Coronavirus wh… ,UNIraq,Iraq,"[('29', 'CARDINAL'), ('PeacekeepersWe', 'ORG'), ('Coronavirus', 'PERSON')]","{'neg': 0.0, 'neu': 0.812, 'pos': 0.188, 'compound': 0.4588}",Iraq
165,, In the new  magazine - out now.  #rethinkingschool #lessonlength #schoolday #timetabling #shadowtimetable #f…,mrdissent,"Scotland, Europe","['', '']","{'neg': 0.0, 'neu': 1.0, 'pos': 0.0, 'compound': 0.0}",UK
166,," The CCP treats different classes of people differently. To enforce quarantine, the lower class may be simply locked (wel…",corona_china,,"[('CCP', 'ORG')]","{'neg': 0.109, 'neu': 0.891, 'pos': 0.0, 'compound': -0.296}",
167,," 116 more police personnel test positive in #Maharashtra, 2,211 total cases Maha Police force#COVID19 #coronavirus #Coronavir…",vallabhthanvi,,"[('116', 'CARDINAL'), ('Maharashtra', 'MONEY'), ('2,211', 'CARDINAL'), ('Maha Police', 'ORG'), '']","{'neg': 0.0, 'neu': 0.806, 'pos': 0.194, 'compound': 0.5574}",
168,, More #coronavirus deaths reported today than last Thursday in the U.K. As #lockdown eases I feel uneasy Not sure I want t…,mrpolll,Dorchester ,"[('today', 'DATE'), ('last Thursday', 'DATE'), ('U.K.', 'GPE')]","{'neg': 0.24, 'neu': 0.664, 'pos': 0.095, 'compound': -0.3578}",USA
169,,29-05-2020:#CoronaVirus Updates for #Haryana:Since Yesterday- New cases: 123- New Recoveries: 43- Deaths: 1To… ,covbot_19,,"[('29', 'CARDINAL'), ('Haryana', 'PERSON'), ('New Recoveries', 'GPE'), ('1To', 'CARDINAL')]","{'neg': 0.0, 'neu': 1.0, 'pos': 0.0, 'compound': 0.0}",
170,,Marketing agency  sets up Covid-19 testing lab at its Derbyshire HQ for staff and their families… ,businesslive,UK,[],"{'neg': 0.0, 'neu': 1.0, 'pos': 0.0, 'compound': 0.0}",United Kingdom
171,, More #coronavirus deaths reported today than last Thursday in the U.K. As #lockdown eases I feel uneasy Not sure I want t…,SadieOaktree100,,"[('today', 'DATE'), ('last Thursday', 'DATE'), ('U.K.', 'GPE')]","{'neg': 0.24, 'neu': 0.664, 'pos': 0.095, 'compound': -0.3578}",
172,," #BREAKING: Hong Kong sees more than a dozen confirmed #coronavirus infection after two weeks of subsidence, multiple lo…",Julia_Famularo,,"[('Hong Kong', 'GPE'), ('more than a dozen', 'CARDINAL'), ('two weeks', 'DATE')]","{'neg': 0.0, 'neu': 1.0, 'pos': 0.0, 'compound': 0.0}",
173,,"The number of #cars built in the UK last month plunged by 99.7%.Just 197 cars were made, according to stark indus… ",telebusiness,London,"['', ('UK', 'GPE'), ('last month', 'DATE'), ('99.7%.Just 197', 'CARDINAL')]","{'neg': 0.0, 'neu': 0.939, 'pos': 0.061, 'compound': 0.0772}",UK
174,,Human trials of four Indian #coronavirus vaccines soon#CoronavirusIndia #COVID19 ,ptcnews,"Mohali, India","[('four', 'CARDINAL'), ('Indian', 'NORP')]","{'neg': 0.0, 'neu': 1.0, 'pos': 0.0, 'compound': 0.0}",India
175,," Boris Johnson has been accused of ""Trumpesque"" behaviour after intervening to stop the government's top experts from an…",FayaBogush,"UK, Devon","[('Boris Johnson', 'PERSON'), ('Trumpesque', 'WORK_OF_ART')]","{'neg': 0.208, 'neu': 0.708, 'pos': 0.085, 'compound': -0.3818}",UK
176,,  Children  are prone to get infections easily.. #coronavirus camn be deadly to them.. Let's t…,tapanchowdhury9,Goaltore,"[('coronavirus', 'PERSON')]","{'neg': 0.0, 'neu': 1.0, 'pos': 0.0, 'compound': 0.0}",India
177,, Is building public housing an answer to the current #EconomicSlump? BTW Despite  referring to #coronavirus as…,cathyCh63485635,"Eatons Hill, Brisbane","[('EconomicSlump', 'PERSON')]","{'neg': 0.0, 'neu': 1.0, 'pos': 0.0, 'compound': 0.0}",Australia
178,, The World Is Still Far From Herd Immunity for #CoronavirusUK ~7% seroprevalence but with ~38K de…,gojohn10,"Fremont, CA","[('The World Is Still Far From Herd Immunity', 'ORG'), ('~38K de…', 'PERSON')]","{'neg': 0.0, 'neu': 1.0, 'pos': 0.0, 'compound': 0.0}",USA
179,," ""The #Covid19 pandemic has resulted in the worst worker safety crisis in OSHA's 50-year history.”Democrat lawmakers accuse…",MannuMellow,Scarif ,"[('OSHA', 'ORG')]","{'neg': 0.328, 'neu': 0.56, 'pos': 0.112, 'compound': -0.7506}",Error
180,, UK researchers try to crack genetic riddle of COVID-19  #coronavirus #research ,HPBlok,,"[('UK', 'GPE'), '']","{'neg': 0.0, 'neu': 1.0, 'pos': 0.0, 'compound': 0.0}",
181,," ""The mortality [rate] in our hospital is very, very high.""Cemeteries are overflowing in Yemen as #coronavirus-related deat…",WeAreLUAN,"Barreiro, BH","[('Yemen', 'GPE')]","{'neg': 0.0, 'neu': 1.0, 'pos': 0.0, 'compound': 0.0}",Brazil
182,, It took  one day to issue an #ExecutiveOrder because he was upset Twitter called him out on his lies.I…,TheNotoriousKCA,,"[('one day', 'DATE'), ('ExecutiveOrder', 'MONEY')]","{'neg': 0.126, 'neu': 0.874, 'pos': 0.0, 'compound': -0.3818}",
183,," Vital emergency Govt funding has helped, but #LocalGov could need as much as £6bn more to cover the financial impact of #coro…",JoBeavis,"England, United Kingdom","[('Vital', 'ORG'), ('Govt', 'ORG'), ('LocalGov', 'PERSON'), ('as much as £6bn', 'MONEY')]","{'neg': 0.077, 'neu': 0.855, 'pos': 0.068, 'compound': -0.0516}",UK
184,,"     Just like the independent inquiry for searching origin of #coronavirus, CCP would not let…",xoxobyyan,,"[('CCP', 'ORG')]","{'neg': 0.0, 'neu': 0.839, 'pos': 0.161, 'compound': 0.3612}",
185,,#Pakistan 🇵🇰 recorded highest ever cases 2638 and deaths 57 in 24 hours due to #coronavirusWake up Govt.Rule is s… ,iamAffanIdrees,"Islamabad, Pakistan","[('Pakistan', 'PERSON'), ('2638', 'DATE'), ('57', 'CARDINAL'), ('24 hours', 'TIME'), ('coronavirusWake', 'MONEY'), ('Govt', 'ORG')]","{'neg': 0.0, 'neu': 1.0, 'pos': 0.0, 'compound': 0.0}",Pakistan
186,, It took  one day to issue an #ExecutiveOrder because he was upset Twitter called him out on his lies.I…,indivisible_py,,"[('one day', 'DATE'), ('ExecutiveOrder', 'MONEY')]","{'neg': 0.126, 'neu': 0.874, 'pos': 0.0, 'compound': -0.3818}",
187,, More #coronavirus deaths reported today than last Thursday in the U.K. As #lockdown eases I feel uneasy Not sure I want t…,Jennyfurfuls,"Born London, now Hereford.","[('today', 'DATE'), ('last Thursday', 'DATE'), ('U.K.', 'GPE')]","{'neg': 0.24, 'neu': 0.664, 'pos': 0.095, 'compound': -0.3578}",UK
188,, The World Is Still Far From Herd Immunity for #CoronavirusUK ~7% seroprevalence but with ~38K de…,NSMCcomLTD1,"Cambridge, England","[('The World Is Still Far From Herd Immunity', 'ORG'), ('~38K de…', 'PERSON')]","{'neg': 0.0, 'neu': 1.0, 'pos': 0.0, 'compound': 0.0}",UK
189,," Amidst the #coronavirus crisis, #India recently witnessed a significant IP dispute between Hindustan Unilever (HUL) and Re…",Sahastranshu2,,"['', ('India', 'GPE'), ('IP', 'ORG'), ('Hindustan Unilever', 'PERSON')]","{'neg': 0.315, 'neu': 0.602, 'pos': 0.083, 'compound': -0.7184}",
190,, More than 200 schools across South Korea forced to return to online teaching days after students are allowed back into cl…,dlspratt,"Los Angeles, CA","[('More than 200', 'CARDINAL'), ('South Korea', 'GPE'), ('days', 'DATE')]","{'neg': 0.13, 'neu': 0.87, 'pos': 0.0, 'compound': -0.4588}",USA
191,, Americans don’t trust Trump. He has been completely unprepared in handling the #coronavirus crisis. And he continues to mak…,rcrisanto1,"Los Angeles, CA","[('Americans', 'NORP'), ('Trump', 'PERSON'), '']","{'neg': 0.168, 'neu': 0.697, 'pos': 0.135, 'compound': -0.2023}",USA
192,," Vital emergency Govt funding has helped, but #LocalGov could need as much as £6bn more to cover the financial impact of #coro…",ASCAPPG,United Kingdom,"[('Vital', 'ORG'), ('Govt', 'ORG'), ('LocalGov', 'PERSON'), ('as much as £6bn', 'MONEY')]","{'neg': 0.077, 'neu': 0.855, 'pos': 0.068, 'compound': -0.0516}",United Kingdom
193,," World Is Still Far From Herd Immunity for #Coronavirus.Even in the hardest-hit cities in the world, vast majority of…",MngelesdelBro,"Barcelona, España","[('Coronavirus', 'PERSON')]","{'neg': 0.0, 'neu': 1.0, 'pos': 0.0, 'compound': 0.0}",Spain
194,, 🇨🇳 #China pledges largest-ever economic rescue package to save jobs and livelihoods amid #coronavirus - SCMP*Li Keqiang con…,Interneconomics,New York City,"[('China', 'GPE')]","{'neg': 0.0, 'neu': 0.625, 'pos': 0.375, 'compound': 0.8126}",USA
195,," . reports for  from #JamiaNagar, a densely populated and predominantly #Muslim area in South East Delhi…",psychobeware,,"[('JamiaNagar', 'PERSON'), ('Muslim', 'NORP'), ('South East Delhi', 'LOC')]","{'neg': 0.0, 'neu': 1.0, 'pos': 0.0, 'compound': 0.0}",
196,," Taiwan Railways, High Speed Rail services to allow food from June 1#coronavirus #COVID19 https…",lydhblog,,"[('Taiwan', 'GPE'), ('June 1#coronavirus', 'DATE')]","{'neg': 0.0, 'neu': 0.872, 'pos': 0.128, 'compound': 0.2263}",
197,, Symptoms of a brain tumor can be general or specific. A general symptom is caused by the pressure of the tumor on the br…,BasaniMasinge,,"[('Symptoms', 'ORG')]","{'neg': 0.28, 'neu': 0.72, 'pos': 0.0, 'compound': -0.7506}",
198,, Helpful map here of the foodbanks currently operating in Islington during the #coronavirus #lockdown: …,Flo_williamson,Islington,"[('Helpful', 'ORG'), ('Islington', 'ORG'), '']","{'neg': 0.0, 'neu': 0.823, 'pos': 0.177, 'compound': 0.4215}",UK
199,," . is this true👇?If yes,do you have an alternative plan in place?Are #ventilators, scarce?If #ICUs are runn…",divyangpat,Bharat ,[],"{'neg': 0.0, 'neu': 1.0, 'pos': 0.0, 'compound': 0.0}",USA
200,, It took  one day to issue an #ExecutiveOrder because he was upset Twitter called him out on his lies.I…,kellyeggs,,"[('one day', 'DATE'), ('ExecutiveOrder', 'MONEY')]","{'neg': 0.126, 'neu': 0.874, 'pos': 0.0, 'compound': -0.3818}",
201,," The team and I love to hear from our teachers about how Sparx is helping, we are so happy we can make a difference no matter…",Saryloo,,"[('Sparx', 'PERSON')]","{'neg': 0.066, 'neu': 0.6, 'pos': 0.334, 'compound': 0.8733}",
202,,HS2 has been exploring ‘hygienic’ railway designs for years  #HS2 #construction #coronavirus ,Robbiehorgs,London,"[('years', 'DATE'), ('HS2', 'PERSON')]","{'neg': 0.0, 'neu': 1.0, 'pos': 0.0, 'compound': 0.0}",UK
203,,"#DidYouKnow that last month we had 10,001 appointments with young people, their families or people supporting them!… ",HealthyYM,,"[('last month', 'DATE'), ('10,001', 'CARDINAL')]","{'neg': 0.0, 'neu': 0.834, 'pos': 0.166, 'compound': 0.4926}",
204,," Wearing a face mask has become an uncomfortable fact of life as Europeans leave lockdown. But for deaf people, it has become…",mitch8951,Europe,"[('Europeans', 'NORP')]","{'neg': 0.167, 'neu': 0.833, 'pos': 0.0, 'compound': -0.4215}",Europe
205,, CDC Admits COVID Death Rate for Healthy People Is 0.02%!#CoronaVirus #Covid19 ,oceanusR337,"Great Lakes, US~Canada","[('CDC', 'ORG')]","{'neg': 0.228, 'neu': 0.468, 'pos': 0.304, 'compound': 0.0}",The Great Lakes
206,, How does Japan manage to bring the #coronavirus pandemic under control w/o nationwide lockdown?#Masks4All…,NSMCcomLTD1,"Cambridge, England","[('Japan', 'GPE'), ('lockdown?#Masks4All', 'CARDINAL')]","{'neg': 0.0, 'neu': 1.0, 'pos': 0.0, 'compound': 0.0}",UK
207,," 7,466 #coronavirus cases in India in 24 hours, biggest jump so far  ",Dimple27486149,"New Delhi, India","[('7,466 #coronavirus', 'MONEY'), ('India', 'GPE'), ('24 hours', 'TIME')]","{'neg': 0.0, 'neu': 1.0, 'pos': 0.0, 'compound': 0.0}",India
208,,"  offered condolences to the famiky of Khalid Sher Dil, martyred in the unfortunate #karachiPlaneCrash. Khalid was…",basit_k19,"Dubai, United Arab Emirates","[('Khalid Sher Dil', 'PERSON'), ('Khalid', 'PERSON')]","{'neg': 0.167, 'neu': 0.833, 'pos': 0.0, 'compound': -0.4588}",Dubai - United Arab Emirates
209,, More than 200 schools across South Korea forced to return to online teaching days after students are allowed back into cl…,EdgarMvnoz,"Los Angeles, CA","[('More than 200', 'CARDINAL'), ('South Korea', 'GPE'), ('days', 'DATE')]","{'neg': 0.13, 'neu': 0.87, 'pos': 0.0, 'compound': -0.4588}",USA
210,, George Orwell Is Rolling Over in His Grave as the World Becomes More Dsytopian Than 1984.#COVID19 #CoronaVirus https…,privateur,,"[('George Orwell', 'PERSON'), ('CoronaVirus', 'PERSON')]","{'neg': 0.133, 'neu': 0.867, 'pos': 0.0, 'compound': -0.3818}",
211,,"Hey  Donny boy, between 100,000 dead #coronavirus victims, #MinneapolisUprising burning down a city… ",donaldrwinslow,"Austin, TX and Rome, Italy","[('Donny', 'PERSON'), ('between 100,000', 'CARDINAL'), ('MinneapolisUprising', 'PERSON')]","{'neg': 0.398, 'neu': 0.602, 'pos': 0.0, 'compound': -0.765}",USA
212,, This week’s update on our response to #coronavirus is now available on our website - here is a data snapshot of some of the…,glenchisholm,Ipswich,"[('This week', 'DATE')]","{'neg': 0.0, 'neu': 1.0, 'pos': 0.0, 'compound': 0.0}",USA
213,," Everything Trump does is a distraction. He wants you to focus on anything other than the pain of 100,000 U.S. deaths and…",tboug,,"[('Trump', 'PERSON'), ('100,000', 'CARDINAL'), ('U.S.', 'GPE')]","{'neg': 0.237, 'neu': 0.763, 'pos': 0.0, 'compound': -0.7096}",
214,," CDC new data show &gt;60,000 health care workers have been infected by the #coronavirus, and close to 300 have died from #COV…",NSMCcomLTD1,"Cambridge, England","[('CDC', 'ORG'), ('close to 300', 'CARDINAL'), ('COV', 'PERSON')]","{'neg': 0.234, 'neu': 0.655, 'pos': 0.11, 'compound': -0.5574}",UK
215,,"Comparison of #coronavirus  infection, recovery and testing rates internationally.#StayAtHomeSaveLives ",_PaulMonaghan,"Ireland, Scotland",[],"{'neg': 0.0, 'neu': 1.0, 'pos': 0.0, 'compound': 0.0}",UK
216,," #CovidTalk - Meet the Nigerian filmmaker 📽️  who created the #Coronavirus monster, an animated #video for tea…",BashorunAkin,Fela's Shrine samplin Afrobeat,"[('Nigerian', 'NORP'), ('Coronavirus', 'PERSON')]","{'neg': 0.0, 'neu': 0.882, 'pos': 0.118, 'compound': 0.25}",Error
217,," The Health Secretary was told it's ""not a laughing matter"" as he guffawed through questions on whether the Test and Trace…",pipmason,"Exeter, England","[('Health', 'ORG')]","{'neg': 0.171, 'neu': 0.829, 'pos': 0.0, 'compound': -0.4023}",UK
218,, British children need to be back in school. British parents need to be back at work. Britain needs #SpaceXDragon up its…,thornedella,,"[('British', 'NORP'), ('British', 'NORP'), ('Britain', 'GPE'), ('SpaceXDragon', 'MONEY')]","{'neg': 0.0, 'neu': 1.0, 'pos': 0.0, 'compound': 0.0}",
219,," 7,466 #coronavirus cases in India in 24 hours, biggest jump so far  ",renatarecreio,brasil,"[('7,466 #coronavirus', 'MONEY'), ('India', 'GPE'), ('24 hours', 'TIME')]","{'neg': 0.0, 'neu': 1.0, 'pos': 0.0, 'compound': 0.0}",Brazil
220,," ""The mortality [rate] in our hospital is very, very high.""Cemeteries are overflowing in Yemen as #coronavirus-related deat…",Twenty1314,,"[('Yemen', 'GPE')]","{'neg': 0.0, 'neu': 1.0, 'pos': 0.0, 'compound': 0.0}",
221,," Experts predict that Brazil will surpass 125,000 #COVID19 deaths by August 4.By comparison, the US is expected to rea…",donal_bisanzio,"Nottingham, England","[('Brazil', 'GPE'), ('125,000 #COVID19', 'MONEY'), ('August 4.By', 'DATE'), ('US', 'GPE')]","{'neg': 0.0, 'neu': 1.0, 'pos': 0.0, 'compound': 0.0}",UK
222,, Every Covid Briefing. Ever. FULL sketch: #Covid19UK #Covid19 #Coronavirus #StayAlert …,alihinspain,"Region of Murcia, Spain","[('FULL', 'ORG'), '', ('StayAlert', 'PERSON')]","{'neg': 0.0, 'neu': 1.0, 'pos': 0.0, 'compound': 0.0}",Spain
223,," Taiwan Railways, High Speed Rail services to allow food from June 1#coronavirus #COVID19 https…",BeAu_NmN,,"[('Taiwan', 'GPE'), ('June 1#coronavirus', 'DATE')]","{'neg': 0.0, 'neu': 0.872, 'pos': 0.128, 'compound': 0.2263}",
224,, This piece is about the lack of public mourning for so many US deaths from #coronavirus.  Public mourning not welcomed by d…,ProfSunnySingh,"London, England","[('US', 'GPE')]","{'neg': 0.36, 'neu': 0.64, 'pos': 0.0, 'compound': -0.8456}",UK
225,,"Chinese team helps Serbia build lab for COVID-19 testing, train personnel #China #Serbia #COVID19 #coronavirus",CCTV_Plus,CHINA,"[('Chinese', 'NORP'), ('Serbia', 'GPE')]","{'neg': 0.0, 'neu': 0.843, 'pos': 0.157, 'compound': 0.3818}",China
226,," . 🐦 is a business built on memes, collaboration, and design and they’re making the #Coronavirus cry. 🦠 😢 Full s…",chethnaamenon,,"[('Coronavirus', 'PERSON')]","{'neg': 0.171, 'neu': 0.829, 'pos': 0.0, 'compound': -0.4767}",
227,,Reopening Offices Post COVID – Safety Tips  &amp; Sanitizing Options#PostCovid19 #Work… ,proimprint,"NC, USA","[('Offices Post', 'ORG'), ('Work', 'MONEY')]","{'neg': 0.0, 'neu': 0.763, 'pos': 0.237, 'compound': 0.4215}",USA
228,, Commisioner  following WHO guide lines for aggressive testing of #coronavirus… ,Jaydipsinh2808,"Ankleshwar, India","[('Commisioner', 'PERSON')]","{'neg': 0.151, 'neu': 0.849, 'pos': 0.0, 'compound': -0.1531}",India
229,," Besides food and ration, the organisation has supplied 1,500 sanitary pads to commercial sex workers and poor women, an…",Dineshd27678248,,"[('1,500', 'CARDINAL')]","{'neg': 0.147, 'neu': 0.853, 'pos': 0.0, 'compound': -0.4767}",
230,," Killing 101,000+ Americans by mismanaging the #coronavirus isn't enough, now  is threatening to just shoot Am…",rachel_maria65,Soros Garret,"[('101,000', 'CARDINAL'), ('Americans', 'NORP')]","{'neg': 0.44, 'neu': 0.56, 'pos': 0.0, 'compound': -0.8807}",Error
231,," ""Piers Corbyn talks about the #Coronavirus #Covid19 #Lockdown and why we must resist the 'Test and Trace' Phone Apps &amp;…",Get_Ginvolved,,"[('Piers Corbyn', 'WORK_OF_ART'), '', ('Lockdown', 'PERSON')]","{'neg': 0.0, 'neu': 1.0, 'pos': 0.0, 'compound': 0.0}",
232,, It took  one day to issue an #ExecutiveOrder because he was upset Twitter called him out on his lies.I…,Kiefer_XJ,"Roselle Park, NJ or Oklahoma","[('one day', 'DATE'), ('ExecutiveOrder', 'MONEY')]","{'neg': 0.126, 'neu': 0.874, 'pos': 0.0, 'compound': -0.3818}",USA
233,," In last 24 hours, 116 police personnel have tested positive for #Coronavirus in Maharashtra and 3 personnel have died due to the v…",namitajoshi20,"Navi Mumbai, India","[('last 24 hours', 'TIME'), ('116', 'CARDINAL'), ('Coronavirus', 'PERSON'), ('Maharashtra', 'ORG'), ('3', 'CARDINAL')]","{'neg': 0.132, 'neu': 0.735, 'pos': 0.132, 'compound': 0.0}",India
234,," #BREAKING: Hong Kong sees more than a dozen confirmed #coronavirus infection after two weeks of subsidence, multiple lo…",AnthonyTNguyen3,"San Diego, CA","[('Hong Kong', 'GPE'), ('more than a dozen', 'CARDINAL'), ('two weeks', 'DATE')]","{'neg': 0.0, 'neu': 1.0, 'pos': 0.0, 'compound': 0.0}",USA
235,," Akira Yoshino, who won a  in Chemistry, posted a video online to help lift the spirits of students negativel…",CoryAnnMary,Rennes,"[('Akira Yoshino', 'PERSON'), ('Chemistry', 'ORG')]","{'neg': 0.0, 'neu': 0.701, 'pos': 0.299, 'compound': 0.7506}",France
236,," Killing 101,000+ Americans by mismanaging the #coronavirus isn't enough, now  is threatening to just shoot Am…",bjsbook,Iowa,"[('101,000', 'CARDINAL'), ('Americans', 'NORP')]","{'neg': 0.44, 'neu': 0.56, 'pos': 0.0, 'compound': -0.8807}",USA
237,, Wow! Look at these numbers! Can’t wait to hear Dr. Fauci and the CDC explain why it is that #coronavirus preferred to str…,wacee5,U.S.A,"[('Fauci', 'PERSON'), ('CDC', 'ORG'), ('coronavirus', 'PERSON'), ('str', 'ORG')]","{'neg': 0.0, 'neu': 0.834, 'pos': 0.166, 'compound': 0.658}",United States
238,, Delhi: Traffic congestion at Delhi-Gurugram border after Haryana government on Thursday sealed borders with the national capi…,LucknawiRooh,Delhi NCR/Lucknow/Chennai,"[('Delhi', 'GPE'), ('Delhi-Gurugram', 'ORG'), ('Haryana', 'GPE'), ('Thursday', 'DATE')]","{'neg': 0.0, 'neu': 1.0, 'pos': 0.0, 'compound': 0.0}",National Capital Region
239,," ICYMI: CEOs from some of India's top #oil, #gas, #shipping companies share insights on the #coronavirus pandemic, trade flow…",Gravity_v20,"visakhapatnam, India","[('ICYMI', 'ORG'), ('India', 'GPE'), '', '']","{'neg': 0.0, 'neu': 0.81, 'pos': 0.19, 'compound': 0.4588}",India
240,,"Although we don't recommend going out to stargaze, for those #amateur #astronomers who are determined to do so duri… ",CosmosPnw,"Portland, OR",[''],"{'neg': 0.098, 'neu': 0.79, 'pos': 0.112, 'compound': 0.0747}",USA
241,, -45.2lbs #weightloss in 115 days! :) #weightlossjourney going well considering #coronavirus has changed everyone's 2020 pla…,DaveEDanna,"Rock Hill, SC","[('weightloss', 'PERSON'), ('115 days', 'DATE'), ('weightlossjourney', 'PERSON'), ('2020', 'DATE')]","{'neg': 0.0, 'neu': 0.722, 'pos': 0.278, 'compound': 0.6588}",USA
242,," I'm sorry, , what?  You think I pay you $1000 for a phone you get to push an operating system that includes the abil…",lfh1744,"Texas, USA","[('1000', 'MONEY')]","{'neg': 0.124, 'neu': 0.876, 'pos': 0.0, 'compound': -0.1779}",USA
243,," Allah says ""Never shall you attain to righteousness unless you spend out of that which you love"". (Al-Quran 3 : 92)…",MaheenSidra,India,"[('Al-Quran', 'PERSON'), ('92', 'CARDINAL')]","{'neg': 0.0, 'neu': 1.0, 'pos': 0.0, 'compound': 0.0}",India
244,," Boris Johnson has been accused of ""Trumpesque"" behaviour after intervening to stop the government's top experts from an…",slogess,"Broughty Ferry, Scotland","[('Boris Johnson', 'PERSON'), ('Trumpesque', 'WORK_OF_ART')]","{'neg': 0.208, 'neu': 0.708, 'pos': 0.085, 'compound': -0.3818}",UK
245,, #Coronavirus updates:• Thailand reports 11 new #COVID19 cases• Colombia extends national quarantine until July• Surge in…,aabello25,Lagos,"[('Coronavirus', 'PERSON'), ('Thailand', 'GPE'), ('11', 'CARDINAL'), '', ('Colombia', 'GPE'), ('Surge', 'PERSON')]","{'neg': 0.0, 'neu': 0.909, 'pos': 0.091, 'compound': 0.128}",Nigeria
246,,  Children  are prone to get infections easily.. #coronavirus camn be deadly to them.. Let's t…,DhanyaAjikesh,Kottayam ,"[('coronavirus', 'PERSON')]","{'neg': 0.0, 'neu': 1.0, 'pos': 0.0, 'compound': 0.0}",India
247,,"Whoever invents a #coronavirus vaccine will control the #patent – and, importantly, who gets to use it… ",NikkiLengkeek,"Sydney, New South Wales",[],"{'neg': 0.0, 'neu': 0.859, 'pos': 0.141, 'compound': 0.3182}",Australia
248,," #CoronaVirusUpdates: 2,636 new #coronavirus cases surfaced in #Pakistan over last 24 hours, taking the tally to 64,028 h…",mumaralid,Driver,"[('2,636', 'CARDINAL'), ('Pakistan', 'GPE'), ('64,028', 'CARDINAL')]","{'neg': 0.0, 'neu': 1.0, 'pos': 0.0, 'compound': 0.0}",USA
249,, Delhi: Traffic congestion at Delhi-Gurugram border after Haryana government yesterday sealed borders with the national capital due…,varung123,"Dwarka, New Delhi","[('Delhi', 'GPE'), ('Delhi-Gurugram', 'ORG'), ('Haryana', 'GPE'), ('yesterday', 'DATE')]","{'neg': 0.0, 'neu': 1.0, 'pos': 0.0, 'compound': 0.0}",India
250,,#Occupy2.0 has commenced. It will not end until the #NeofascistDNCGOP are eliminated #coronavirus #COVID__19  #MFA… ,davidsirias1,"Portland, OR ","[('Occupy2.0', 'PERSON'), '']","{'neg': 0.0, 'neu': 1.0, 'pos': 0.0, 'compound': 0.0}",USA
251,,"LOCKDOWN: VIDEO on how to wash hands proper ly, watch here:  #coronavirussa #coronavirus… ",tolatender,South Africa,[''],"{'neg': 0.0, 'neu': 0.769, 'pos': 0.231, 'compound': 0.5574}",South Africa
252,," The idea of “slow streets,” where lanes of traffic are taken out for pedestrians or restaurant patios, is coming to Vancouver,…",CraigRMcCulloch,Vancouver (Burnaby),"[('Vancouver', 'GPE')]","{'neg': 0.0, 'neu': 1.0, 'pos': 0.0, 'compound': 0.0}",Canada
253,," Inline with our country's efforts in fighting #Coronavirus, &amp; in addition to Kingdom Hospital's efforts, We put the…",pingpongpongpon,"Lahore, Pakistan","[('Inline', 'GPE'), ('Coronavirus', 'PERSON'), (""Kingdom Hospital's"", 'ORG')]","{'neg': 0.128, 'neu': 0.872, 'pos': 0.0, 'compound': -0.3612}",Pakistan
254,," The Centers for Disease Control (CDC), has recommended that the public and employees at the workplace wear masks at all…",Kandiwapa11,22°33'33.9' S   17°4'59.6'' E,"[('The Centers for Disease Control', 'ORG'), ('CDC', 'ORG')]","{'neg': 0.0, 'neu': 0.913, 'pos': 0.087, 'compound': 0.2023}",Error
255,, Private Sale is running --&gt; #blockchain #privatesale #token #funds #covir #coronavirus #decentralize…,septianairmal29,"Jawa Tengah, Indonesia","['', '']","{'neg': 0.0, 'neu': 1.0, 'pos': 0.0, 'compound': 0.0}",Indonesia
256,, Thanks for the update. But will Twitter be fact checking Communist China’s lies about the #coronavirus? What about Chin…,GaryjJeffrey,"California, USA","[('Communist', 'NORP'), ('China', 'GPE'), ('Chin', 'PERSON')]","{'neg': 0.123, 'neu': 0.749, 'pos': 0.128, 'compound': 0.0258}",USA
257,, #MenstruationMatters for you#MenstruationMatters for me#MenstruationMatters for her#MenstruationMatters for him#Menstruation…,shoaib00001,"Islamabad, Pakistan","[('MenstruationMatters', 'PERSON')]","{'neg': 0.0, 'neu': 1.0, 'pos': 0.0, 'compound': 0.0}",Pakistan
258,,"In a constantly changing industry and in these tumultuous times, it’s important to keep up to date with what is hap… ",PeopleMedical,"Hamilton, Brisbane",[],"{'neg': 0.0, 'neu': 0.913, 'pos': 0.087, 'compound': 0.2023}",Australia
259,, A radical11-point plan to save lives proposing “a further lockdown of care homes” was submitted to Downing St on 28 Apr…,JulieBJewellery,Buckinghamshire,"[('Downing St', 'ORG'), ('28', 'CARDINAL')]","{'neg': 0.0, 'neu': 0.738, 'pos': 0.262, 'compound': 0.7506}",UK
260,," Journalists asking Vallance and Whitty for their view on Cummings matter. PM intervenes and stops them from answering, sa…",Coopersphere,Southampton,"[('Vallance', 'ORG'), ('Cummings', 'ORG')]","{'neg': 0.081, 'neu': 0.863, 'pos': 0.056, 'compound': -0.128}",USA
261,,Wor king from home is a solution for Small Businesses amid COVID-19 Social Distancing. Read more:… ,tolatender,South Africa,"[('Small Businesses amid COVID-19', 'WORK_OF_ART')]","{'neg': 0.0, 'neu': 0.859, 'pos': 0.141, 'compound': 0.3182}",South Africa
262,, Delhi: Traffic congestion at Delhi-Gurugram border after Haryana government on Thursday sealed borders with the national capi…,TOIGurgaon,,"[('Delhi', 'GPE'), ('Delhi-Gurugram', 'ORG'), ('Haryana', 'GPE'), ('Thursday', 'DATE')]","{'neg': 0.0, 'neu': 1.0, 'pos': 0.0, 'compound': 0.0}",
263,, #Coronavirus has not stopped Modi-Shah's police to target Muslim students for participating in anti-citizenship act protest!!…,adilkhan202025,Praying for AAP,"[('Coronavirus', 'PERSON'), (""Modi-Shah's"", 'ORG'), ('Muslim', 'NORP')]","{'neg': 0.0, 'neu': 0.87, 'pos': 0.13, 'compound': 0.3071}",Error
264,, A #Taiwan #Tourism promotional item designed by popular local #Manga illustrator Zuo Hsuan is expected to help attract vi…,Taiwanderful,Taiwan,"[('Tourism', 'PERSON'), ('Manga', 'PERSON'), ('Zuo Hsuan', 'PERSON')]","{'neg': 0.0, 'neu': 0.652, 'pos': 0.348, 'compound': 0.7906}",Taiwan
265,, What might be the learnings of #coronavirus ?Death of capitalism as we know it Populist leaders are dangerousGreen economy…,Keven85972982,Hong Kong,"[('coronavirus', 'PERSON')]","{'neg': 0.178, 'neu': 0.822, 'pos': 0.0, 'compound': -0.5994}",Hong Kong
266,,Hollywood star  donated a second batch of plasma to help fight the #coronavirus. The actor shared a phot… ,SamaaEnglish,"Formerly FATA, Balochistan via Karachi, and definitely Pakistan","[('Hollywood', 'GPE'), ('second', 'ORDINAL')]","{'neg': 0.126, 'neu': 0.628, 'pos': 0.246, 'compound': 0.3612}",Pakistan
267,, #Turkey recorded the lowest daily #coronavirus infections since 25 March 2020 and the lowest number of deaths since 29 March…,annisahh21,,"[('Turkey', 'GPE'), ('25 March 2020', 'DATE'), ('29', 'CARDINAL')]","{'neg': 0.221, 'neu': 0.723, 'pos': 0.055, 'compound': -0.5994}",
268,, I have written a letter to Hon. Prime Minister Shri. Narendra Modi to express my deep concern over the current scenario of…,TanveerNadaf02,,"[('Hon', 'ORG'), ('Shri', 'PERSON'), ('Narendra Modi', 'PERSON')]","{'neg': 0.0, 'neu': 1.0, 'pos': 0.0, 'compound': 0.0}",
269,," Everything Trump does is a distraction. He wants you to focus on anything other than the pain of 100,000 U.S. deaths and…",bunigephoto,"Centerville, GA","[('Trump', 'PERSON'), ('100,000', 'CARDINAL'), ('U.S.', 'GPE')]","{'neg': 0.237, 'neu': 0.763, 'pos': 0.0, 'compound': -0.7096}",USA
270,, COACHING Student Sudalai.. #coronaVirus #DMKFails ,VSivasithan,,[''],"{'neg': 0.0, 'neu': 1.0, 'pos': 0.0, 'compound': 0.0}",
271,, What Do Countries With The Best #Coronavirus Responses Have In Common? Women Leaders. What do countries with the worst #Coro…,PixSantos,"London, England","[('Coro', 'PERSON')]","{'neg': 0.156, 'neu': 0.684, 'pos': 0.16, 'compound': 0.0258}",UK
272,," 7,466 #coronavirus cases in India in 24 hours, biggest jump so far  ",TilsonFrancis,"Indi, India","[('7,466 #coronavirus', 'MONEY'), ('India', 'GPE'), ('24 hours', 'TIME')]","{'neg': 0.0, 'neu': 1.0, 'pos': 0.0, 'compound': 0.0}",India
273,," As we are grieving the loss of 100,000 souls in America to the #coronavirus that has disproportionately impacted communitie…",wwredpepper,,"[('100,000', 'CARDINAL'), ('America', 'GPE')]","{'neg': 0.248, 'neu': 0.752, 'pos': 0.0, 'compound': -0.6808}",
274,,This is the #shithole that #orangefuckface   and the #shitforbrains in the  … ,IronMonkeee,City of Warriors,"['', '']","{'neg': 0.0, 'neu': 1.0, 'pos': 0.0, 'compound': 0.0}",USA
275,,"Akira Yoshino, who won a  in Chemistry, posted a video online to help lift the spirits of students negat… ",The_Japan_News,"Tokyo, Japan","[('Akira Yoshino', 'PERSON'), ('Chemistry', 'ORG')]","{'neg': 0.0, 'neu': 0.701, 'pos': 0.299, 'compound': 0.7506}",Japan
276,,We need more ppl like ! ❤️ He is actually the one who is majorly contributing fr a win against… ,xNooriiiex,New Delhi ,[],"{'neg': 0.0, 'neu': 0.692, 'pos': 0.308, 'compound': 0.7983}",India
277,," . is this true👇?If yes,do you have an alternative plan in place?Are #ventilators, scarce?If #ICUs are runn…",nitaldave,,[],"{'neg': 0.0, 'neu': 1.0, 'pos': 0.0, 'compound': 0.0}",
278,," Omg, this is a terribly damning indictment of this govt's handling of the #coronavirus crisis. The number of #COVID19 de…",Femulator,"East Suffolk England, UK EU","[('Omg', 'PERSON'), '']","{'neg': 0.383, 'neu': 0.568, 'pos': 0.049, 'compound': -0.8689}",UK
279,,"We can no more break the chain, we should think like everyone is +ve and be in isolation at home for 14days and tho… ",lifeofram86,Madras,"[('14days', 'DATE')]","{'neg': 0.173, 'neu': 0.739, 'pos': 0.088, 'compound': -0.34}",India
280,,How private hospitals are on a wild looting spree for #coronavirusVideo by Av… ,BKanad,"Jambudwipe, Bharatkhande",[],"{'neg': 0.0, 'neu': 1.0, 'pos': 0.0, 'compound': 0.0}",Error
281,," World Is Still Far From Herd Immunity for #Coronavirus.Even in the hardest-hit cities in the world, vast majority of…",jrdelbrio,Barcelona,"[('Coronavirus', 'PERSON')]","{'neg': 0.0, 'neu': 1.0, 'pos': 0.0, 'compound': 0.0}",Spain
282,, It took  one day to issue an #ExecutiveOrder because he was upset Twitter called him out on his lies.I…,nelskj,,"[('one day', 'DATE'), ('ExecutiveOrder', 'MONEY')]","{'neg': 0.126, 'neu': 0.874, 'pos': 0.0, 'compound': -0.3818}",
283,, AMC Commisioner  following WHO guide lines for aggressive testing of #coronavirus He was transferred.Gujarat…,tarunlakhanIYC,"Gujarat, India","[('AMC Commisioner', 'ORG'), ('Gujarat', 'PERSON')]","{'neg': 0.11, 'neu': 0.89, 'pos': 0.0, 'compound': -0.1531}",India
284,, Statement from  on changes to #coronavirus lockdown restrictions announced today by  …,TattyBojangles7,,"['', ('today', 'DATE')]","{'neg': 0.0, 'neu': 1.0, 'pos': 0.0, 'compound': 0.0}",
285,, #Coronavirus #COVID19 #Japan - Post-virus era begins for Tokyo's nightlife. #AFP📸  ,antoningalleau,Ailleurs,"[('Tokyo', 'GPE'), ('AFP', 'PERSON')]","{'neg': 0.0, 'neu': 1.0, 'pos': 0.0, 'compound': 0.0}",Error
286,, ‘Naming the Lost’ on the fence outside of Green-Wood Cemetery #NewYork #NYC where people have left tributes to remember tho…,SWNS,International,"[('Green-Wood Cemetery', 'LOC'), '']","{'neg': 0.0, 'neu': 1.0, 'pos': 0.0, 'compound': 0.0}",USA
287,, OPINION: Not up for debate - #Nigeria's best players are overseas  #Football #Rohr #SuperEagles #…,ScoreNigeria1,,[],"{'neg': 0.0, 'neu': 0.756, 'pos': 0.244, 'compound': 0.6369}",
288,, It took  one day to issue an #ExecutiveOrder because he was upset Twitter called him out on his lies.I…,GreenTerelle,,"[('one day', 'DATE'), ('ExecutiveOrder', 'MONEY')]","{'neg': 0.126, 'neu': 0.874, 'pos': 0.0, 'compound': -0.3818}",
289,," ""The mortality [rate] in our hospital is very, very high.""Cemeteries are overflowing in Yemen as #coronavirus-related deat…",TilsonFrancis,"Indi, India","[('Yemen', 'GPE')]","{'neg': 0.0, 'neu': 1.0, 'pos': 0.0, 'compound': 0.0}",India
290,, Gonna keep retweeting this everytime  I see it. #PrinceWilliam #coronavirus,ATrulyFan,España,"[('Gon', 'PERSON'), ('PrinceWilliam', 'PERSON')]","{'neg': 0.0, 'neu': 1.0, 'pos': 0.0, 'compound': 0.0}",Spain
291,, A radical11-point plan to save lives proposing “a further lockdown of care homes” was submitted to Downing St on 28 Apr…,sylviehj,headcorn,"[('Downing St', 'ORG'), ('28', 'CARDINAL')]","{'neg': 0.0, 'neu': 0.738, 'pos': 0.262, 'compound': 0.7506}",UK
292,," BJP accuses Govt of Maharashtra, Chattisgarh, Rajasthan, Jharkhand, Punjab, West Bengal, Delhi, Kerala, Telangana, Andhr…",InvestMENA,dUbAi,"[('BJP', 'ORG'), ('Govt of Maharashtra', 'ORG'), ('Chattisgarh', 'DATE'), ('Rajasthan', 'GPE'), ('Jharkhand', 'GPE'), ('Punjab', 'PERSON'), ('West Bengal', 'GPE'), ('Delhi', 'GPE'), ('Kerala', 'GPE'), ('Telangana', 'GPE')]","{'neg': 0.146, 'neu': 0.854, 'pos': 0.0, 'compound': -0.34}",Dubai - United Arab Emirates
293,,"Total number of Coronavirus positive cases in the country rises to 165,799 (including 89,987 active, 71,105 cured/d… ",NewsAurChai,Mumbai,"[('Coronavirus', 'ORG'), ('165,799', 'CARDINAL'), ('89,987', 'CARDINAL'), ('71,105', 'CARDINAL')]","{'neg': 0.0, 'neu': 0.648, 'pos': 0.352, 'compound': 0.765}",India
294,,Delhi: Traffic congestion at Delhi-Gurugram border after Haryana government on Thursday sealed borders with the nat… ,TOIDelhi,"New Delhi, India","[('Delhi', 'GPE'), ('Delhi-Gurugram', 'ORG'), ('Haryana', 'GPE'), ('Thursday', 'DATE')]","{'neg': 0.0, 'neu': 1.0, 'pos': 0.0, 'compound': 0.0}",India
295,," 7,466 #coronavirus cases in India in 24 hours, biggest jump so far  ",Azad_Offical,"Kolkata, India","[('7,466 #coronavirus', 'MONEY'), ('India', 'GPE'), ('24 hours', 'TIME')]","{'neg': 0.0, 'neu': 1.0, 'pos': 0.0, 'compound': 0.0}",India
296,,Secure your next role. We are here to help - book your #free Career Consultation to learn how we can guide you thro… ,NALExecs,Worldwide,[''],"{'neg': 0.0, 'neu': 0.797, 'pos': 0.203, 'compound': 0.6249}",USA
297,,เช้านี้ตื่นมาพร้อมกับนมถั่วเหลืองอุ่นๆและขนมทำเอง 🤦🏻‍♀️ Happy Friday na ja ❤️ Days 64 National Alert Level 4… ,anna_patcharee,South Africa,"[('Friday', 'DATE'), ('Days 64', 'DATE'), ('4', 'CARDINAL')]","{'neg': 0.0, 'neu': 0.651, 'pos': 0.349, 'compound': 0.7096}",South Africa
298,,Washing your hands is always an important activity to incorporate into your office routine. Download WASH YOUR HA… ,wshyourhandsapp,,[],"{'neg': 0.0, 'neu': 0.904, 'pos': 0.096, 'compound': 0.2023}",
299,," ""The mortality [rate] in our hospital is very, very high.""Cemeteries are overflowing in Yemen as #coronavirus-related deat…",MtlSeb,"Mont-Tremblant, Québec","[('Yemen', 'GPE')]","{'neg': 0.0, 'neu': 1.0, 'pos': 0.0, 'compound': 0.0}",Canada
300,, It took  one day to issue an #ExecutiveOrder because he was upset Twitter called him out on his lies.I…,timthehuman666,Southeast Michigan,"[('one day', 'DATE'), ('ExecutiveOrder', 'MONEY')]","{'neg': 0.126, 'neu': 0.874, 'pos': 0.0, 'compound': -0.3818}",USA
301,," Gisele Sanchez leaves a tribute w/ her brother Edwin Rojas’s for their recently passed aunt Rosa Moran Duran, on a noticebo…",SWNS,International,"[('Gisele Sanchez', 'PERSON'), ('Edwin Rojas', 'PERSON'), ('Rosa Moran Duran', 'PERSON')]","{'neg': 0.0, 'neu': 1.0, 'pos': 0.0, 'compound': 0.0}",USA
302,," Closed for cleaning: A Tyson Food pork processing plant in Iowa where 555 of 2,517 employees have tested positive for #COVID19…",Ahuman_beeing,"Austin, TX","[('Tyson Food', 'ORG'), ('Iowa', 'GPE'), ('555', 'CARDINAL'), ('2,517', 'CARDINAL')]","{'neg': 0.0, 'neu': 0.841, 'pos': 0.159, 'compound': 0.5574}",USA
303,, #CoronavirusAustralians Urge Queensland To Keep Border Closed Indefinitely.  you can keep em we don't want em…,oldjoeschmo,Melbourne Australia,[],"{'neg': 0.075, 'neu': 0.925, 'pos': 0.0, 'compound': -0.0572}",Australia
304,, Do join in at 6 pm on Instagram as I discuss challenges of reporting a global pandemic #coronavirus send in your questions too!…,varung123,"Dwarka, New Delhi","[('6 pm', 'TIME'), ('Instagram', 'NORP')]","{'neg': 0.0, 'neu': 0.826, 'pos': 0.174, 'compound': 0.4199}",India
305,," 7, 466 New #Coronavirus cases reported in last 24 hours Highest Spike in cases ...",CyrilAlexande10,,"[('7', 'CARDINAL'), ('466', 'CARDINAL'), ('Coronavirus', 'PERSON'), ('last 24 hours', 'TIME')]","{'neg': 0.0, 'neu': 1.0, 'pos': 0.0, 'compound': 0.0}",
306,, 🇸🇦🇸🇦Pledging the support of  companies to our government &amp; country in the fight against #Coronavirus#WeA…,mmubkhan,Oman,"[('🇸🇦🇸', 'ORG'), ('Coronavirus#WeA', 'PERSON')]","{'neg': 0.142, 'neu': 0.71, 'pos': 0.148, 'compound': 0.0258}",Oman
307,,A dedicated helpline has been introduced to advise people living with #diabetes who need help with insulin througho… ,ELHT_NHS,East Lancashire,[],"{'neg': 0.0, 'neu': 0.725, 'pos': 0.275, 'compound': 0.6908}",UK
308,,What will the potential impact of the #coronavirus pandemic be on the #mentalhealth of both students and teachers?… ,GovtEvents,"London, England",[''],"{'neg': 0.0, 'neu': 1.0, 'pos': 0.0, 'compound': 0.0}",UK
309,," 5-day Remdesivir dose works as well as the 10-day dose in COVID-19, study finds  Via  #Biophar…",helensbiggamble,,"[('Remdesivir', 'PERSON'), ('10-day', 'DATE'), ('Via', 'GPE'), ('Biophar', 'PERSON')]","{'neg': 0.0, 'neu': 0.877, 'pos': 0.123, 'compound': 0.2732}",
310,," 7,466 #coronavirus cases in India in 24 hours, biggest jump so far  ",saddam_mulani,,"[('7,466 #coronavirus', 'MONEY'), ('India', 'GPE'), ('24 hours', 'TIME')]","{'neg': 0.0, 'neu': 1.0, 'pos': 0.0, 'compound': 0.0}",
311,, The #coronavirus crisis can further increase the dependency of poorer countries on #China. Read our white paper to learn more:…,viriyabot,Internet,"['', ('China', 'GPE')]","{'neg': 0.255, 'neu': 0.656, 'pos': 0.089, 'compound': -0.6486}",USA
312,,This week’s update on our response to #coronavirus is now available on our website - here is a data snapshot of som… ,IpswichGov,"Ipswich, Suffolk, UK","[('This week', 'DATE')]","{'neg': 0.0, 'neu': 1.0, 'pos': 0.0, 'compound': 0.0}",UK
313,, Traffic snarls as Haryana seals border with Delhi due to rising #coronavirus cases in the state. ,MeghnaCDavid,Bangalore,"[('Haryana', 'ORG'), ('Delhi', 'GPE')]","{'neg': 0.0, 'neu': 1.0, 'pos': 0.0, 'compound': 0.0}",India
314,, HE'S THE 3RD PERSON TO CATCH THE MAR-A-LARGO FLU.The mayor of Miami has COVID-19 and has been updating the public da…,reykevster,"Bodfish, CA","[('Miami', 'GPE')]","{'neg': 0.0, 'neu': 1.0, 'pos': 0.0, 'compound': 0.0}",USA
315,," 7, 466 New #Coronavirus cases reported in last 24 hours Highest Spike in cases ...",JabajKh83864396,"महराजगंज,युपी,भारत","[('7', 'CARDINAL'), ('466', 'CARDINAL'), ('Coronavirus', 'PERSON'), ('last 24 hours', 'TIME')]","{'neg': 0.0, 'neu': 1.0, 'pos': 0.0, 'compound': 0.0}",India
316,,"It’s only been a four-day week, but we are still just as excited as ever for the weekend ahead! 🙌🏼May this weeken… ",mysocialhousing,UK,"[('four-day week', 'DATE'), ('the weekend ahead', 'DATE')]","{'neg': 0.0, 'neu': 0.855, 'pos': 0.145, 'compound': 0.5255}",United Kingdom
317,, Join a pre-recorded discussion with three global leaders on the forefront of the #COVID19 pandemic as they discuss both th…,Gmal25459724,مكة المكرمة,"[('three', 'CARDINAL')]","{'neg': 0.0, 'neu': 0.891, 'pos': 0.109, 'compound': 0.296}",Mecca Saudi Arabia
318,,"The Ukraine riot is a PAID performance, it is not real. #COVID19 #CORONAVIRUS",important_2021,,"[('Ukraine', 'GPE')]","{'neg': 0.247, 'neu': 0.753, 'pos': 0.0, 'compound': -0.5574}",
319,,#Coronavirus restrictions are being relaxed in Scotland after 66 days of full lockdown.Follow the… ,BBCScotlandNews,"Pacific Quay, Glasgow","[('Coronavirus', 'PERSON'), ('Scotland', 'GPE'), ('66 days', 'DATE')]","{'neg': 0.0, 'neu': 0.802, 'pos': 0.198, 'compound': 0.4939}",UK
320,, It took  one day to issue an #ExecutiveOrder because he was upset Twitter called him out on his lies.I…,stinginthetail,"Quietly plotting on Bundjalung Land, Gold Coast, Qld, Australia","[('one day', 'DATE'), ('ExecutiveOrder', 'MONEY')]","{'neg': 0.126, 'neu': 0.874, 'pos': 0.0, 'compound': -0.3818}",Australia
321,, The Arabian Gulf's wealthy nations have also been hard hit by the #coronavirus pandemic.What are they doing to cushion the e…,angprimamang,,"[(""The Arabian Gulf's"", 'LOC')]","{'neg': 0.061, 'neu': 0.83, 'pos': 0.109, 'compound': 0.2732}",
322,," Our Trust Board meeting is taking place this morning. Due to the ongoing #coronavirus pandemic, this meeting is being held as…",kateballinger,"Lawley, Telford, England","[('Our Trust Board', 'ORG'), ('this morning', 'TIME')]","{'neg': 0.0, 'neu': 0.858, 'pos': 0.142, 'compound': 0.5106}",UK
323,,"#WHO, #UNICEF back #DOH in fight against COVID-19  #newsupdate #coronavirus #coronavirus",odnewsonline,Philippines,"[('WHO', 'PERSON'), ('UNICEF', 'ORG'), ('DOH', 'MONEY'), '']","{'neg': 0.206, 'neu': 0.794, 'pos': 0.0, 'compound': -0.3818}",Philippines
324,,"With almost 400,000 reported #coronavirus cases, #brazil has now been included to the list of #travelban countries… ",davieslegal,,"[('almost 400,000', 'CARDINAL'), ('brazil', 'GPE')]","{'neg': 0.0, 'neu': 1.0, 'pos': 0.0, 'compound': 0.0}",
325,," Wearing a face mask has become an uncomfortable fact of life as Europeans leave lockdown. But for deaf people, it has become…",EwiJih,Bullerbyn,"[('Europeans', 'NORP')]","{'neg': 0.167, 'neu': 0.833, 'pos': 0.0, 'compound': -0.4215}",Sweden
326,,Ignorance is the power of #Covid19 I understand Vietnam has a zero death rate due to #coronavirus and remember they… ,swiftuxo,Pretoria,"[('Vietnam', 'GPE'), ('zero', 'CARDINAL')]","{'neg': 0.286, 'neu': 0.714, 'pos': 0.0, 'compound': -0.7506}",South Africa
327,,Working from home is a solution for  Small Businesses amid COVID-19 Social Distancing. Read more:… ,tolajobjobs,South Africa,[],"{'neg': 0.0, 'neu': 0.85, 'pos': 0.15, 'compound': 0.3182}",South Africa
328,,Testing for #coronavirus has been expanded to include anyone over the age of 5 with symptoms. Key workers remain a… ,lutoncouncil,"Luton, Bedfordshire","['', ('the age of 5', 'DATE')]","{'neg': 0.0, 'neu': 1.0, 'pos': 0.0, 'compound': 0.0}",UK
329,,"Renewable energy projects create jobs, save money, say top economists #savingmoney… ",homeselfe,,[],"{'neg': 0.0, 'neu': 0.432, 'pos': 0.568, 'compound': 0.802}",
330,," As we are grieving the loss of 100,000 souls in America to the #coronavirus that has disproportionately impacted communitie…",TheJuliaNelson,"Reno, NV","[('100,000', 'CARDINAL'), ('America', 'GPE')]","{'neg': 0.248, 'neu': 0.752, 'pos': 0.0, 'compound': -0.6808}",USA
331,,"  No better proof that the media doesn't give a rat's ass about #coronavirus  social distancing, who spreads the v…",Pickleboogers,,"[('about #coronavirus', 'MONEY')]","{'neg': 0.096, 'neu': 0.654, 'pos': 0.251, 'compound': 0.5499}",
332,,"""European scientists are developing a #laser sensor that detects #coronavirus at the earliest point of infection fr… ",ZemaxLLC,"Kirkland, WA","[('European', 'NORP')]","{'neg': 0.0, 'neu': 1.0, 'pos': 0.0, 'compound': 0.0}",USA
333,,"#COVID19 #CORONAVIRUS Tracker #Thailand 🇹🇭  🦠Total Cases: 3,076New Cases: 11Deaths: 57 💀… ",GlobalNewsBKK,ความไม่มีโรคเป็นลาภอันประเสริฐ,"[('CORONAVIRUS', 'PERSON'), ('57', 'CARDINAL')]","{'neg': 0.0, 'neu': 1.0, 'pos': 0.0, 'compound': 0.0}",Error
334,,#Sodar is an experiment created by  which is designed to use Augmented Reality (AR) to put a virtual 2 meter… ,K_E_N_J,"Anand, India","[('Sodar', 'PERSON'), ('2 meter', 'QUANTITY')]","{'neg': 0.0, 'neu': 0.895, 'pos': 0.105, 'compound': 0.25}",India
335,,Being constantly on the move... Its important to clean your devices you constantly use every few minutes. As well a… ,Workshop17za,South Africa,"[('every few minutes', 'TIME')]","{'neg': 0.0, 'neu': 0.72, 'pos': 0.28, 'compound': 0.6808}",South Africa
336,,"#COVID19 #CORONAVIRUS Tracker #Thailand 🇹🇭  🦠Total Cases: 3,076New Cases: 11Deaths: 57 💀… ",GlobalNewsTH,Thailand  ไม่มีใครแก่เกินเรียน,"[('CORONAVIRUS', 'PERSON'), ('57', 'CARDINAL')]","{'neg': 0.0, 'neu': 1.0, 'pos': 0.0, 'compound': 0.0}",Error
337,, Indiscriminately spraying peaceful protesters w/ pepper spray **during an airborne pandemic** is one fucked up asshole mo…,tjbogart33,"Boulder, CO",[],"{'neg': 0.268, 'neu': 0.596, 'pos': 0.136, 'compound': -0.4767}",USA
338,,We present to our readers:The Sandsby #Poem #Poetry #SpillWords #coronavirus ,Spill_Words,New York & The World,"[('Sandsby', 'ORG'), ('SpillWords', 'PERSON')]","{'neg': 0.0, 'neu': 1.0, 'pos': 0.0, 'compound': 0.0}",USA
339,,#WFH .  . #benefits . Follow and shift to a #new #workculture . #COVID19 .#StayHome… ,nutrafywellness,"Gurgaon, India","[('WFH', 'PERSON'), ('COVID19', 'MONEY')]","{'neg': 0.0, 'neu': 1.0, 'pos': 0.0, 'compound': 0.0}",India
340,," #China should have stopped #coronavirus at source, will announce 'certain decisions' today: #Trump ",MechRohn,,"[('China', 'GPE'), ('Trump', 'MONEY')]","{'neg': 0.127, 'neu': 0.733, 'pos': 0.14, 'compound': 0.0516}",
341,, Safety FIRST. P U S H: #COVID2019 #LetsFightCovid19 #coronavirus #Social…,MichelleRoseG33,planet Earth ,"[('U S H', 'GPE'), '', '']","{'neg': 0.0, 'neu': 0.682, 'pos': 0.318, 'compound': 0.4215}",USA
342,, Wear a mask. You're protecting others #coronavirus ,e_veritas_unum,,[],"{'neg': 0.0, 'neu': 1.0, 'pos': 0.0, 'compound': 0.0}",
343,,McKinsey On Marketing In The Age Of COVID-19#Engagement #Loyalty #Retail #Marketing… ,linkmobilityuk,"Edinburgh, Scotland","[('McKinsey On Marketing', 'PERSON')]","{'neg': 0.0, 'neu': 1.0, 'pos': 0.0, 'compound': 0.0}",UK
344,,Jerusalem's Al-Aqsa mosque will reopen to worshippers from May 31 with health restrictions after being closed for m… ,the_arabposts,,"[('Jerusalem', 'GPE'), ('Al-Aqsa', 'FAC'), ('May 31', 'DATE')]","{'neg': 0.0, 'neu': 0.904, 'pos': 0.096, 'compound': 0.2023}",
345,," Journalists asking Vallance and Whitty for their view on Cummings matter. PM intervenes and stops them from answering, sa…",MegShaw1,,"[('Vallance', 'ORG'), ('Cummings', 'ORG')]","{'neg': 0.081, 'neu': 0.863, 'pos': 0.056, 'compound': -0.128}",
346,," Journalists asking Vallance and Whitty for their view on Cummings matter. PM intervenes and stops them from answering, sa…",delboyfour,Nottingham,"[('Vallance', 'ORG'), ('Cummings', 'ORG')]","{'neg': 0.081, 'neu': 0.863, 'pos': 0.056, 'compound': -0.128}",UK
347,, AMEN. Touch: #coronavirus #CoronavirusPandemic #COVID19 #Covid19Out #Chi…,MichelleRoseG33,planet Earth ,"[('AMEN', 'ORG'), '', ('Chi', 'PERSON')]","{'neg': 0.0, 'neu': 1.0, 'pos': 0.0, 'compound': 0.0}",USA
348,, I've been looking forward to this....  in Conversation with   from  Priscilla D…,Legaleagle24,"Walthamstow, London","[('Priscilla', 'PERSON')]","{'neg': 0.0, 'neu': 1.0, 'pos': 0.0, 'compound': 0.0}",UK
349,, #Coronavirus has not stopped Modi-Shah's police to target Muslim students for participating in anti-citizenship act protest!!…,Prakash33286763,"Guwahati,Shillong&Delhi","[('Coronavirus', 'PERSON'), (""Modi-Shah's"", 'ORG'), ('Muslim', 'NORP')]","{'neg': 0.0, 'neu': 0.87, 'pos': 0.13, 'compound': 0.3071}",India
350,, Good LUCK. C L I C K: #COVID19 #Covid19usa #coronavirus #CoronaLockdown…,MichelleRoseG33,planet Earth ,"['', ('CoronaLockdown', 'PRODUCT')]","{'neg': 0.0, 'neu': 0.43, 'pos': 0.57, 'compound': 0.7672}",USA
351,, Shielding is the word used to describe how to protect those at highest risk of severe illness if they catch #coronavirus.…,HealthwatchT_W,"Telford, England",[],"{'neg': 0.274, 'neu': 0.63, 'pos': 0.096, 'compound': -0.5859}",UK
352,, The fight against #coronavirus will be won through strong #PrimaryHealthCareIf pandemic of such a magnitude didn't made u…,gluppschlopp,"Chhattisgarh, India","[('coronavirus', 'PERSON'), ('PrimaryHealthCareIf', 'GPE')]","{'neg': 0.11, 'neu': 0.593, 'pos': 0.297, 'compound': 0.6597}",India
353,, #Coronavirus has not stopped Modi-Shah's police to target Muslim students for participating in anti-citizenship act protest!!…,ImranJamima,,"[('Coronavirus', 'PERSON'), (""Modi-Shah's"", 'ORG'), ('Muslim', 'NORP')]","{'neg': 0.0, 'neu': 0.87, 'pos': 0.13, 'compound': 0.3071}",
354,, WIN this WAR. C l I c k:#COVIDー19 #COVID #coronavirus #ChineseVirus #Hea…,MichelleRoseG33,planet Earth ,"[('WIN', 'ORG'), ('WAR', 'ORG'), '']","{'neg': 0.305, 'neu': 0.396, 'pos': 0.299, 'compound': -0.0258}",USA
355,," One person can make all the difference. And in this case, the rest should not try to follow him. Stay home and suppor…",maharashtra,"Maharashtra, India","[('One', 'CARDINAL')]","{'neg': 0.0, 'neu': 1.0, 'pos': 0.0, 'compound': 0.0}",India
356,,Customer Insights that AI Will Change Because of COVID-19#artificialintelligence… ,ChatbotNews,,[],"{'neg': 0.0, 'neu': 1.0, 'pos': 0.0, 'compound': 0.0}",
357,,Customer Insights that AI Will Change Because of COVID-19#artificialintelligence… ,Ebot7Info,info@e-bot7.com,[],"{'neg': 0.0, 'neu': 1.0, 'pos': 0.0, 'compound': 0.0}",Error
358,,Customer Insights that AI Will Change Because of COVID-19#artificialintelligence… ,ChatbotConsult,"Munich, Bavaria",[],"{'neg': 0.0, 'neu': 1.0, 'pos': 0.0, 'compound': 0.0}",Germany
359,,#coronavirus India is now 5th in total Active Cases and 2nd in total Serious/Critical cases. ,maruhgar,Bangalore,"[('India', 'GPE'), ('5th', 'ORDINAL'), ('Active Cases', 'ORG'), ('2nd', 'ORDINAL'), ('Serious/Critical', 'ORG')]","{'neg': 0.0, 'neu': 0.838, 'pos': 0.162, 'compound': 0.4019}",India
360,, #CJPagainstCovid!At CJP India we are mapping aid to marginalised &amp; needy groups impacted by the #coronavirus outbreak.If you…,artsnoise_,"London, England","[('India', 'GPE'), ('&amp', 'ORG')]","{'neg': 0.137, 'neu': 0.863, 'pos': 0.0, 'compound': -0.4003}",UK
361,,"With businesses set to return in the next few days, it's important to know how to keep your business clean and heal… ",AandRcleaning,South Wales,"[('the next few days', 'DATE')]","{'neg': 0.0, 'neu': 0.816, 'pos': 0.184, 'compound': 0.5423}",UK
362,, It took  one day to issue an #ExecutiveOrder because he was upset Twitter called him out on his lies.I…,DandD04,,"[('one day', 'DATE'), ('ExecutiveOrder', 'MONEY')]","{'neg': 0.126, 'neu': 0.874, 'pos': 0.0, 'compound': -0.3818}",
363,,Memphis Airport recommends travelers bring masks:#Aviation #Airport #COVID19 #Coronavirus ,SpeedBird_NCL,Worldwide,"[('Memphis Airport', 'FAC'), ('masks:#Aviation #Airport', 'ORG'), ('Coronavirus', 'PERSON')]","{'neg': 0.0, 'neu': 0.808, 'pos': 0.192, 'compound': 0.2263}",USA
364,, So VC UHS  is ready to die while treating patients (God forbid) but what if we don't want to risk our and o…,MaarwaMajical,,[],"{'neg': 0.141, 'neu': 0.71, 'pos': 0.148, 'compound': 0.0485}",
365,," Journalists asking Vallance and Whitty for their view on Cummings matter. PM intervenes and stops them from answering, sa…",Jeremy83157595,"London, England","[('Vallance', 'ORG'), ('Cummings', 'ORG')]","{'neg': 0.081, 'neu': 0.863, 'pos': 0.056, 'compound': -0.128}",UK
366,,"The Dean of St Paul’s Cathedral, the Very Reverend David Ison, said: “We have been overwhelmed by the response to R… ",city_matters,"City of London, London","[('The Dean of St Paul’s', 'ORG'), ('David Ison', 'PERSON')]","{'neg': 0.0, 'neu': 0.943, 'pos': 0.057, 'compound': 0.0516}",UK
367,,"   , Cummings &amp; all their #Tory cronies will never admit to their abject failures from…",angieprysorjon1,"Oxford, England","[('Cummings &amp', 'ORG'), ('Tory', 'PERSON')]","{'neg': 0.277, 'neu': 0.723, 'pos': 0.0, 'compound': -0.5562}",UK
368,," Sharing a public twitter list of scientists, doctors, and health reporters covering #coronavirus #covid19 I’ve been curating. h…",fibroidsupport,London,[''],"{'neg': 0.0, 'neu': 0.851, 'pos': 0.149, 'compound': 0.4215}",UK
369,,Hospital workers kept in the dark about colleagues' coronavirus tests  … ,Union_NewsUK,On your side,[],"{'neg': 0.0, 'neu': 1.0, 'pos': 0.0, 'compound': 0.0}",USA
370,, There is a cracked relationship with the public&amp;govt over public health messages where there is one rule for an elite adv…,RedBlackWhite8,,"[('public&amp;govt', 'ORG'), ('one', 'CARDINAL')]","{'neg': 0.0, 'neu': 1.0, 'pos': 0.0, 'compound': 0.0}",
371,,#Italy: Extraordinary measures to minimize the impact of #COVID19 on #tax #litigation activities#coronavirus,GComplianceNews,Global,"[('Italy', 'PERSON'), ('COVID19', 'MONEY'), '']","{'neg': 0.0, 'neu': 1.0, 'pos': 0.0, 'compound': 0.0}",USA
372,, The evolving situation with #coronavirus is challenging the research community. It is likely to have a substantial imp…,BHFprofessional,,"[('coronavirus', 'PERSON')]","{'neg': 0.0, 'neu': 0.815, 'pos': 0.185, 'compound': 0.34}",
373,," #COVID19 |Good morning, From 1 June, the country moves to #level3lockdown and most people will be going back to work. Emp…",AChinomwe,"Harare, Zimbabwe","[('1 June', 'DATE'), ('level3lockdown', 'PERSON')]","{'neg': 0.0, 'neu': 1.0, 'pos': 0.0, 'compound': 0.0}",Zimbabwe
374,," 7,466 #coronavirus cases in India in 24 hours, biggest jump so far  ",KrushnaYendru,,"[('7,466 #coronavirus', 'MONEY'), ('India', 'GPE'), ('24 hours', 'TIME')]","{'neg': 0.0, 'neu': 1.0, 'pos': 0.0, 'compound': 0.0}",
375,,"Wearing a face mask has become an uncomfortable fact of life as Europeans leave lockdown. But for deaf people, it h… ",euronews,Europe,"[('Europeans', 'NORP')]","{'neg': 0.174, 'neu': 0.826, 'pos': 0.0, 'compound': -0.4215}",Europe
376,, #Coronavirus has not stopped Modi-Shah's police to target Muslim students for participating in anti-citizenship act protest!!…,KhanAhm08253989,"Saitama-ken, Japan","[('Coronavirus', 'PERSON'), (""Modi-Shah's"", 'ORG'), ('Muslim', 'NORP')]","{'neg': 0.0, 'neu': 0.87, 'pos': 0.13, 'compound': 0.3071}",Japan
377,, Guidance to support education professionals to meet the psychological needs of children as they plan for their return to scho…,RPTeachSEND,,[],"{'neg': 0.0, 'neu': 0.876, 'pos': 0.124, 'compound': 0.4019}",
378,,The outbreak and spread of #coronavirus has affected the global world of work. More people face #redundancy. What s… ,charel_jelles,Benelux,[],"{'neg': 0.082, 'neu': 0.918, 'pos': 0.0, 'compound': -0.1531}",USA
379,,This piece is about the lack of public mourning for so many US deaths from #coronavirus.  Public mourning not welco… ,DrLJBHayes,"Canterbury, England","[('US', 'GPE')]","{'neg': 0.323, 'neu': 0.677, 'pos': 0.0, 'compound': -0.7964}",UK
